<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance</name>
		<image>./00Image/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Baldur's Gate - Dark Alliance (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Baldur's Gate: Dark Alliance is a real time hack and slash Action role-playing game presented in a true 3D perspective correct rotatable third person overhead view. The battle system in the game is simplistic but flexible. Character statistics at the game's beginning are preset, and the player may only customize their character's stats through gaining experience points. Experience points are gained by winning battles, and at specific levels the character gains new ability points to spend on enhancements specific to the character class. The ability choices affect the fighting style of the character.

Gameplay is linear, and any current quest must be completed successfully before the story proceeds. There are also relatively few non-player characters (NPCs), of which only those who are part of a quest or side-quest may be interacted with. There are not that many sidequests available in the game, but those available - such as for Keaira and Ipswitch - help players to gain experience and level up. Weapons, armor and items are only available for purchase from one location at a time in the current region, and are increasingly valuable later in the game.

The game's ruleset is based on a limited set of 3rd Edition Dungeons &amp; Dragons rule-set; compared to other D&amp;D Games there are relatively few rules implemented in the game. There are four playable classes: Human Arcane Archer, Elven Sorceress, Dwarven Fighter and Drow Ranger. Gameplay strategy is different for all characters: the human relies on ranged attacks and stealth, the elf character can cast magic spells, and the dwarf is an all-around fighter. Through updating each character, the characters go to mimic characters of other classes.

A local co-op mode is available, which uses a single non-split screen view. The second player can select one of the unused characters.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Black Isle Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Interplay Entertainment Corp.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./BloodRayne (USA).iso</path>
		<name>BloodRayne</name>
		<image>./00Image/BloodRayne (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/BloodRayne (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/BloodRayne (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/BloodRayne (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>BloodRayne is a killing machine. The Brimstone Society calls upon this half-vampire, half-human agent to take on two missions in the years between the world wars. At the root of these missions is one man who searches for powerful occult artifacts that would bring Germany into a new age of domination. As BloodRayne, you must stop this man's elite Nazi army from releasing terrorizing creatures onto the world.</desc>
		<releasedate>20021015T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Terminal Reality, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Majesco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Bully (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Bully</name>
		<image>./00Image/Bully (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Bully (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Bully (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Bully (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Bully is a story of one Jimmy Hopkins, whose academic success hasn't been anything spectacular as he's been expelled from various schools. His parents have a grand idea of sending him to Bullworth Academy which -- despite its grand name -- houses lots of other kids like Jimmy. This is the place where future dictators, murderers, and mad scientists reside. With a help of a few friends, some wits and hard-as-a-rock fists, Jimmy has to survive through one year in Bullworth Academy.

Often described as 'GTA in high school', the game indeed has many similarities with the famous car-hijacking series. It features a 'sandbox' environment, which encompasses not only the vast high school grounds, but also the nearby town of Bullworth. As in GTA games, the player can choose to complete missions in different order, or simply roam the game world, interacting with the environment and the characters.

Naturally, much of the typical GTA-like content has been changed to fit the high school setting. The violence is still present: Jimmy can punch and kick anyone he encounters, as well as use a variety of (non-lethal) weapons such as slingshots, fire crackers, and even self-made guns. It is not possible to hijack cars, but Jimmy is able to steal and ride bicycles. The missions include a variety of gameplay styles: chases, races, shooter-like sequences, escort missions, spying, random acts of vandalism, and many more.

Bully features a plethora of activities and mini-games that can be accessed outside of the missions. Jimmy can simply attend classes and study. Each class is built like a mini-game: for example, language lesson involves composing as many words as possible out of a few given letters within a time limit. It is possible to find, buy, and wear different outfits, get jobs and earn money, and even date schoolmates and buy presents for them.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061017T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Vancouver</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End</name>
		<image>./00Image/Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Disney Pirates of the Caribbean - At World's End (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>At World's End video games from Disney Interactive Studios invite players to "live and die by the sword" as they venture to the worlds of the films and beyond while playing as Captain Jack Sparrow, Will Turner and Elizabeth Swann.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom Entertainment Software</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy XII (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy XII</name>
		<image>./00Image/Final Fantasy XII (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Final Fantasy XII (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Final Fantasy XII (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Final Fantasy XII (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Final Fantasy XII  takes place in the fictional location of Ivalice, where the empires of Archadia and Rozarria are waging an endless war. Dalmasca, a small kingdom, is caught between the warring nations. When Dalmasca becomes annexed by Archadia, its princess, Ashe, creates a resistance movement. During the struggle, she meets Vaan, a young adventurer who dreams of commanding an airship. They are quickly joined by a band of allies; together, they rally against the tyranny of the Archadian Empire.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War II (USA).iso</path>
		<name>God of War II</name>
		<image>./00Image/God of War II (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/God of War II (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/God of War II (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/God of War II (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Kratos is now the God of War, having defeated the Olympian god Ares. Shunned by the other gods and still haunted by nightmares from his past, Kratos decides to join an army of Spartans in an attack on the city of Rhodes. Kratos also ignores a warning from the goddess Athena that his lust for revenge is alienating the other gods.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070313T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War (USA).iso</path>
		<name>God of War</name>
		<image>./00Image/God of War (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/God of War (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/God of War (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/God of War (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>God of War is an action-adventure game developed by the Santa Monica division of Sony Computer Entertainment. It was released for the Playstation 2 on March 22, 2005. This successful release has spawned multiple sequels and prequels, including God of War II for PlayStation 2, God of War: Chains of Olympus for the PSP, God of War III for the PlayStation 3, God of War: Ghost of Sparta for the PSP and God of War: Ascension for the PS3. The plot of the game is steeped in Greek mythology, and follows a man named Kratos who works in service of the gods as punishment for murdering his wife and child. Later, he becomes intertwined in a battle between the gods themselves and is chosen to kill Ares, the god of war, by using Pandora's Box. God of War received widespread critical acclaim and numerous game of the year awards, and critics praised the outstanding visuals and gameplay. A remastered version of God of War was released on the PlayStation 3 with the God of War Collection, which also included God of War II and bonus content. The remastered game included 2x anti-aliasing and 720p resolution at 60 frames per second. It was released in the U.S. on November 17, 2009. In Japan, the game was published by Capcom.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto III (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto III</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto III (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto III (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto III (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto III (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Liberty City, USA. The worst place in America.

You've been betrayed and left for dead. Now you're taking revenge, unless the city gets you first. Mob bosses need a favor, crooked cops need help and street gangs want you dead. you'll have to rob, steal and kill to stay out of serious trouble.

Anything can happen out there.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto - Liberty City Stories (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>There are a million stories in Liberty City. This one changes everything. Once a trusted wise guy in the Leone crime family, Toni Cipriani was forced into hiding after killing a made man. Now he's back and it's time for things to be put right.

The streets of Liberty City are in turmoil. Warring mafiosi vie for control as the town begins to self-destruct under waves of political corruption, organized crime, drug trafficking and union strikes. No one can be trusted as Toni tries to clean up the mess of the city's chaotic underworld. Deranged hit men, morally depraved tycoons, cynical politicians and his own mother stand in his way as Toni tries to bring the city under Leone control.

Forced to fight for his life in an odyssey that will shake Liberty City to its foundations, Toni must use any means necessary to secure his place in the leadership of the Leone family in a town up for grabs.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060606T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds, Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto - San Andreas (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: San Andreas is a 2004 PlayStation 2 third-person shooter action-adventure sandbox video game developed by Rockstar North and released by Rockstar Games in the USA on October 26, 2004.

Five years ago Carl Johnson escaped from the pressures of life in Los Santos, San Andreas, a city tearing itself apart with gang trouble, drugs and corruption. Where film stars and millionaires do their best to avoid the dealers and gangbangers.

Now, it's the early 90s. Carl's got to go home. His mother has been murdered. His family has fallen apart and his childhood friends are all heading towards disaster. On his return to the neighborhood, a couple of corrupt cops frame him for homicide. CJ is forced on a journey that takes him across the entire state of San Andreas, to save his family and take control of the streets.</desc>
		<releasedate>20041026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City Stories (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Vice City, 1984. Opportunity abounds in a city emerging from the swamps, its growth fueled by the violent power struggle in a lucrative drug trade. Construction is everywhere as a shining metropolis rises from foundations of crime and betrayal.

As a soldier, Vic Vance has always protected his dysfunctional family, his country, himself. One bad decision later and that job is about to get much harder. Kicked out onto the streers of a city torn between glamour and gluttony, Vic is faced with a stark choice - build an empire or be crushed.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds, Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Vice City</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto - Vice City (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Grand Theft Auto: Vice City is a 2002 PlayStation 2 third-person shooter action-adventure sandbox video game developed by Rockstar North and released by Rockstar Games in the USA on October 29, 2002.

Welcome to the 1980's.

Welcome to Vice City, a huge urban sprawl stretching from the beach to the swamps and the glitz to the ghetto, a town brimming with delights and degradation.

Having just made it back onto the streets of Liberty City after a long stretch inside. Tommy Vercetti is sent to Vice City by his old boss, Sonny Forelli. But all does not go smoothly upon his arrival in the glamorous, hedonistic metropolis of Vice City. Tommy is set up and loses everything. Sonny wants his money back, but the biker gangs, Cuban gangsters, and corrupt politicians stand in his way. Most of Vice City seems to want Tommy dead. His only answer is to fight back and take over the city himself.</desc>
		<releasedate>20021029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets</name>
		<image>./00Image/Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harry Potter and the Chamber of Secrets (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>In this Harry Potter game, join him during his second term at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.

A dark plot against his 'Mudblood' classmates has Harry befuddled as more and more students are strangely petrified. Harry must learn new spells and cast them without mistake to uncover the secrets and solve the mysteries.

Interact with familiar characters from the movie: Ron, Hermoine and, of course, Gilderoy Lockhart. Additionally, there are multiple mini-games and side quests.</desc>
		<releasedate>20021115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (Europe).iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix</name>
		<image>./00Image/Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harry Potter and the Order of the Phoenix (Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>Based off the fifth book and movie of the series, players take control of Harry Potter in this 3D adventure as he faces the dangers of his fifth year of Hogwarts, avoiding the malicious Professor Dolores Umbridge, builds Dumbledore's Army, and faces off with Voldemort himself as the prophecy continues to unfold.

Players will navigate through the castle of Hogwarts and beyond, learning fifth year spells, solving multiple puzzles, avoiding traps, and even get a chance to play as the Weasley brothers, Sirius Black and Dumbledore himself.

Survive the year, learn new spells, and survive one of the darkest battles in Harry's life as he faces his first real battle against Voldemort, 'He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named'!</desc>
		<releasedate>20070625T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban</name>
		<image>./00Image/Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Offering a host of new features and opponents, Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban looks to offer fans of this series a refreshingly new storyline as Harry and friends face their most terrifying opponents yet. For the first time in the series, gamers will be able to switch between Harry's friends, Ron Weasley and Hermione Granger, to face challenges and overcome enemies using the specific skills each character possesses. Together, their strengths will need to be combined and their spells mastered, as they unravel the mystery surrounding Sirius Black and his escape from the notorious wizard prison, Azkaban. Revealing these secrets and solving the mystery will not be easy, as sub-quests, creatures, and the mystery of the Marauder's Map all block the path that will lead players to the finale on the shore of the great lake at Hogwarts.</desc>
		<releasedate>20040604T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA UK</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</name>
		<image>./00Image/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The most famous boy wizard's first-year adventure gets a next generation update as Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone comes to PlayStation 2, Xbox, and Nintendo GameCube in this reissue of the title. The updated release features presentational enhancements designed to make use of the power of the 128-bit generation systems. The gameplay and story remain true to the initial release (which was designed for home computers and the original PlayStation): a third-person 3D action-adventure based on Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, the first novel in J.K. Rowling's explosively popular series. 

Players take the role of the prodigious young magician as he begins his first year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, joined by other favorite characters such as Ron Weasley, Hermione Granger, and even Draco Malfoy. Harry Potter can explore the grounds at Hogwarts, spend time with Hagrid, and even join a quick game of quidditch. However as in the novel, Harry's special gifts are noticed not only by his instructors but by darker forces as well, and he may even come face-to-face with "You-Know-Who" himself before this adventure is over.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Warthog</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup</name>
		<image>./00Image/Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harry Potter - Quidditch World Cup (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Harry Potter: Quidditch World Cup is a 2003 video game produced by EA Games and EA Sports that features the fictional sport of Quidditch from the Harry Potter franchise. The user plays in the Hogwarts Quidditch Cup competition, competing amongst the four houses of Hogwarts: Gryffindor, Slytherin, Hufflepuff and Ravenclaw. Players victorious in the house competition qualify for the Quidditch World Cup, competing against the United States, England, France, Germany, The Nordic Countries, Japan, Spain, Australia and Bulgaria.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031107T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Games</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jak II (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Jak II</name>
		<image>./00Image/Jak II (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Jak II (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Jak II (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Jak II (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The game begins with Jak and Daxter, the protagonists, and Samos, their guardian, watching as Keira, Samos’ daughter and Jak’s love interest, demonstrate the Rift Rider and Precursor Rift Gate that they found in the previous game. When activated, the Rift opens a portal, and a large ominous atmosphere and a monster appear. Jak launches the Rider through the gate, past the monster. Jak and Daxter, separated from Keira and Samos, arrive in the segregated dystopia known as Haven City. They are separated on arrival, and Jak is captured by the city's Krimzon Guard. While Jak is imprisoned, he undergoes experiments with Dark Eco under the command of the city's leader: Baron Praxis. Jak, along with previous prisoners in the city jail, were experimented on for Operation: Dark Warrior, a project that consisted of injecting prisoners with dark eco in order to give them super-human abilities to be used in Haven City's war against animalistic creatures called Metal Heads. Jak, the only prisoner to survive the experiments, is altered mentally and physically, turning him (temporarily under random and controlled spasms) into a deadly monster.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031014T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kingdom Hearts II (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Kingdom Hearts II</name>
		<image>./00Image/Kingdom Hearts II (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Kingdom Hearts II (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Kingdom Hearts II (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Kingdom Hearts II (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Sora, Donald, and Goofy are back in the third installment (second for PS2) of the Kingdom Hearts series, continuing where Kingdom Hearts: Chain of Memories left off. The trio awakens from their sleep and goes to Twilight Town. When the game begins, you will first have control over a boy name Roxas who wields a dual-Keyblade. He is trying to enjoy the remainder of his summer vacation with his friends but he keeps having flash-backs of someone else's memories.

When he meets up with Sora, the two learns they have a special connection with one another. Afterwards, the group will continue their search for King Mickey and Riku. This time, they will travel to new worlds and work with various characters from the Disney and Final Fantasy universes. This includes worlds from not only Disney's animated movies but other movies as well like Pirates of the Caribbean and TRON.

In Kingdom Hearts II, Sora and his friends will battle various enemies including the Heartless from Kingdom Hearts, but also a group of enemies called Nobodies. Nobodies are "nonexistent beings" who are under the control of Organization XIII - a group of 13 members in black coats that Sora and his friends have reduced down to just half.

Gameplay is very similar to Kingdom Hearts: the player controls Sora with Donald and Goofy helping with their magic and attacks. Sora can use various magic powers as well as use Summon which will call upon the aid of special Disney characters that will temporarily fight alongside him. A new feature of combat are "Reaction Commands". Some enemies will leave themselves open during attacks, and if the player presses the Reaction Command button when prompted Sora will take advantage of the situation, either turning an enemy's attack against them, striking from a defenseless side for extra damage, or avoiding an otherwise unavoidable attack. As the trio levels up and progresses in the game they will gain new abilities that they can equip. Also, after Mickey meets the party, if Sora is KO'd the player will have the option of controlling Mickey and defending Sora until he can recover.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060328T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square Enix</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil</name>
		<image>./00Image/Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Klonoa 2 - Lunatea's Veil (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Klonoa, a long-eared creature, has stumbled on yet another mystical adventure. In Klonoa 2, a dark kingdom threatens the enchanted realm of Lunatea. Now it's up to Klonoa and his friends, Lolo and Popka, to prevent evil forces from bringing monsters and sickness into their world. Help Klonoa through 24 magical stages featuring hover-board gliding, perceptual changes, and new treacherous foes. On your adventure, you'll drop off waterfalls, get shot into the air by cannon, and gain special abilities from your defeated enemies.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary</name>
		<image>./00Image/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Lara Croft Tomb Raider - Anniversary (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Lara Croft Tomb Raider: Anniversary is a remake of the original Tomb Raider. The remake has the same basic storyline, locations, and core gameplay; however, it has a technically more advanced graphics engine and adds several new features that were introduced in Lara Croft Tomb Raider: Legend. Lara has many new moves, such as swinging on ropes, bullet time when an animal rushes towards her, and the addition of a grappling hook in her inventory (which resembles the one from the original game). Jumping is also a lot easier, as the heroine automatically grabs the ledges without requiring pixel-precise timing. There are also completely new moves, where Lara balances and jumps on small sticks.

The cutscenes are identical, but rendered in real-time using the new engine. Some are also action-based, like in the previous games, requiring quick reflexes to keep the action going. The environments and puzzles have been somewhat changed to fit the new gameplay, and the voice recording was also redone.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070605T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Spyro, The - Dawn of the Dragon (USA).iso</path>
		<name>The Legend of Spyro - Dawn of the Dragon</name>
		<image>./00Image/Legend of Spyro, The - Dawn of the Dragon (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Spyro, The - Dawn of the Dragon (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Spyro, The - Dawn of the Dragon (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Legend of Spyro, The - Dawn of the Dragon (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Free from his imprisonment, the Dark Master unleashes his wrath upon the world, determined to bring forth a new age of darkness. As evil spreads over the world like a plague, Spyro must discover abilities beyond that of the elements and unlock the true power of the purple dragon within him if he is to stop the Dark Master and fulfill his destiny.</desc>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Etranges Libellules</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Max Payne (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Max Payne</name>
		<image>./00Image/Max Payne (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Max Payne (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Max Payne (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Max Payne (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The story is told in medias res and consists of three volumes: "The American Dream", "A Cold Day in Hell", and "A Bit Closer to Heaven". The game begins in the winter of 2001, as New York City finishes experiencing the worst blizzard in the history of the city. The intro sequence shows Max Payne, a renegade DEA agent and former NYPD officer, standing at the top of a skyscraper building as police units arrive. He then experiences a flashback from three years ago. Back in 1998, Max returned home to find that a trio of apparent junkies had broken into his house while high on a new designer drug called Valkyr. Max rushed to the aid his family, but was too late and his wife and their newborn daughter had already been brutally murdered. After his family's funeral, Payne transferred to the DEA.
Three years later, Max Payne is employed as an undercover operative inside the Punchinello Mafia family responsible for the trafficking of Valkyr. His DEA colleague B.B. gives Max a message asking him to meet another DEA agent, who is also Max's best friend, Alex Balder, in the NYC Subway station. Max's arrival at the subway results in a shoot-out after he encounters mobsters working for Jack Lupino, a Mafia underboss in the Punchinello crime family, attempting a bank robbery by breaking through from the station. Working his way back to the surface, Max encounters Alex, who is then killed by an unknown assassin and Payne becomes the prime suspect in the murder. Additionally, the Mafia find out that he is a cop and now want him dead.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Remedy Entertainment, Rockstar Toronto</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mercury Meltdown Remix (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mercury Meltdown Remix</name>
		<image>./00Image/Mercury Meltdown Remix (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mercury Meltdown Remix (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mercury Meltdown Remix (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mercury Meltdown Remix (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The goo has gotten onto your big-screen TV with this remixed version of the popular PSP puzzler now on PS2. Mercury Meltdown is a brain-teasing puzzle game that challenges players to immerse themselves in a colorful world of sci-fi machines, crazy characters and bubbling test tubes. Players take control of a liquid mercury 'blob', guiding it around traps, door switches, spikes, moving floors and other hazardous elements in order to complete the level. This remix features over 200 thought provoking levels, including two never-before seen Labs.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061128T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ignition Banbury</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Okami (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Okami</name>
		<image>./00Image/Okami (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Okami (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Okami (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Okami (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Ōkami (Japanese: 大神, lit. "great god" or "great spirit") is an action-adventure video game developed by Clover Studio and published by Capcom. It was released for PlayStation 2 in 2006 in Japan and North America, and in 2007 in Europe and Australia. After the closure of Clover Studio a few months after the release, a port for Wii was developed by Ready at Dawn, Tose, and Capcom, and released in 2008.

Set in classical Japan, Ōkami combines Japanese mythology and folklore to tell the story of how the land was saved from darkness by the Shinto sun goddess, named Amaterasu, who took the form of a white wolf. It features a sumi-e-inspired cel-shaded visual style and the Celestial Brush, a gesture-system to perform miracles. The game was planned to use more traditional realistic rendering, but this had put a strain on the graphics processing of the PlayStation 2. Clover Studio switched to a cel-shaded style to reduce the processing, which led to the Celestial Brush concept. The gameplay is modeled on The Legend of Zelda, one of director Hideki Kamiya's favorite series. The game's name is a pun, as "ōkami" can mean either "great god" (大神) or "wolf" (狼) in Japanese.

Ōkami was one of the last PlayStation 2 games released prior to the release of the PlayStation 3. Although it suffered from poor sales, the game received critical acclaim, earning IGN's 2006 Game of the Year. The Wii version earned similar praise, though the motion control scheme received mixed reviews. A high-definition port, remastered by Capcom and HexaDrive, was released on the PlayStation 3 via the PlayStation Network in October 2012 and for retail in Japan in November, supporting the use of the PlayStation Move motion controller. The port was released for PlayStation 4, Windows, and Xbox One in December 2017 worldwide, for the Nintendo Switch in August 2018, and for Amazon Luna in April 2022. Mainstream adoption of the game has improved with the release of these remasters, and Ōkami is considered to be one of the best video games ever made, as well as an example of video games as an art form, aided by the improved art details and graphics resolutions.

A spiritual successor on the Nintendo DS, Ōkamiden, was released in Japan in September 2010, followed by North America and Europe in March 2011.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070209T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Clover Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow</name>
		<image>./00Image/Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pirates of the Caribbean - The Legend of Jack Sparrow (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The game begins with Jack Sparrow and Will Turner trying to steal an object from a Spanish fortress in Panama. They are double-crossed and captured. While facing the gallows (and while Jack looks for an escape route as always), he begins to retell some of his stories to Will Turner, albeit exaggerated and not completely honestly; for instance, he always claims that either Will Turner or Elizabeth Swann was with him, even when they insist they have no idea what he's talking about. These stories include how Jack sacked Nassau Port without firing a shot; how he escaped from the desert island on the backs of sea turtles (which he never did prove in the first movie); how he fought a Chinese sorceress named Madame Tang; encountered a legion of frozen Norse warriors; visited the Arctic; and a complete retelling of Curse of the Black Pearl, complete with sequences that never happened and lines that were never said.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060628T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bethesda Softworks</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Primal (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Primal</name>
		<image>./00Image/Primal (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Primal (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Primal (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Primal (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Jen meets a short gargoyle named Scree, who informs her that while she must leave the physical plane Mortalis and accompany him to the demon plane Oblivion. The creature who kidnapped Lewis and left her for dead is an agent of Abaddon who represents Chaos and has been locked in struggle for aeons with Arella, representing Order. The balance between Chaos and Order has been upset and it is Jen's task to restore the balance, all the while hoping to discover the whereabouts of Lewis.

Primal can be described as a "3D platformer", being somewhat similar in its basic gameplay mechanics to Tomb Raider games. Puzzle-solving and action-based combat constitute the focus of the gameplay. The player can switch between Jen and Scree at any time; Jen is capable of fighting, but Scree is invulnerable to enemy attacks. When Jen is incapacitated in combat, Scree must quickly restore her to life within a time limit; failure to do so prematurely ends the game.

Combat is heavily based on "finishing moves" and Jen's ability to transform into demonic forms. There are four demons Jen can merge herself with; they are obtained one by one as the game's narrative advances. These demonic forms allow Jen to use special abilities, which include jumping to extreme heights, unnaturally fast swimming, slowing down time, and using powerful weapons.</desc>
		<releasedate>20030325T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ratchet & Clank (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Ratchet & Clank</name>
		<image>./00Image/Ratchet & Clank (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ratchet & Clank (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ratchet & Clank (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Ratchet & Clank (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Ratchet &amp; Clank is a platform/adventure game in a similar vein to the 3D versions of the Rayman, Sonic, Mario, or other games. It involves the two protagonists Ratchet, a furry alien creature, and Clank, a nerdy little robot, going on a quest to find Captain Qwark and ultimately to help save the galaxy.

Ratchet &amp; Clank includes many of the best features of previous similar games, but makes itself unique in a number of ways. Firstly each of the game's levels are huge sweeping vistas with extremely detailed buildings which are visible at all times (i.e. there is no distance fog). This means that a building on the horizon is not just a "backdrop"; in all likelihood Ratchet will be exploring it in a few moments time. Secondly, the game includes a number of sub-games, such as a space fight sequence and a number of turret shoot-outs which are akin to Missile Command in the first person.

The game has over twenty levels (planets) and includes as many real-time cut-scenes which tell the story. Also of note is that the story is non-linear, requiring the player to return to previous levels to complete objectives and to choose between multiple paths forward. There is also a respectable array of weapons, gadgets, and accessories to find or buy as the game progresses, which offer some unique gameplay features.</desc>
		<releasedate>20021104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>SCEE</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scaler (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Scaler</name>
		<image>./00Image/Scaler (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Scaler (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Scaler (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Scaler (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Scaler is a 3D platform game with elements of combat, stealth, and puzzle-solving. Upon accidentally uncovering his neighbor's evil plot to take over the universe with an army of mutant lizards, Bobby "Scaler" Johnson is put in the position to infiltrate the operation and bring it down from the inside. He is transported to another dimension and transformed into a lizard himself. The enemy army is strong and diverse, however, with different mutant lizard soldier types that are well suited for various tasks.

Luckily, after transforming from a boy into a lizard, changing from one lizard form to another eventually becomes relatively easy, and Scaler will need to assume the appearance and abilities of no fewer than five other creatures in order to accomplish all the objectives before him.

Since certain goals can only be reached in one particular lizard form, part of the challenge can be figuring out which shape to take in each situation. Nevertheless, whether they realize it or not, all the good people of universe are depending on Scaler to prevent the impending mutant lizard uprising. Needless to say, perhaps, players expecting a serious, realistic, simulation-style game may be somewhat disappointed with Scaler.</desc>
		<releasedate>20041026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Artificial Mind &amp; Movement</developer>
		<publisher>Global Star Software Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scarface - The World Is Yours (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Scarface - The World Is Yours</name>
		<image>./00Image/Scarface - The World Is Yours (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Scarface - The World Is Yours (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Scarface - The World Is Yours (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Scarface - The World Is Yours (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Miami in the '80s: gangs, drugs and hookers dominate the scene and a Cuban called Tony Montana rises up to be the most powerful drug dealer, controlling the whole of Miami. This is the story of the 1983 movie Scarface in which Tony Montana dies during a attack from a rival gang on his mansion at the end. The game now puts the player in the shoes of Tony a few moments before the gang hits his office.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061008T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra | Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights</name>
		<image>./00Image/Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Scooby-Doo! Night of 100 Frights (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The Mastermind has kidnapped Mystery Inc, and it's up to Scooby-Doo to search for his lost friends. Guide Scooby through 12 huge levels that include a creepy mansion, a spooky cave, a ghostly graveyard, and a perilous pier. As you search for clues, you must avoid classic Scooby-Doo monsters, use wacky inventions, eat Scooby Snacks, and gather power-ups. Do you have what it takes to foil the Mastermind's plan to rid the world of Mystery Inc?</desc>
		<releasedate>20020520T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heavy Iron Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadow of the Colossus (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Shadow of the Colossus</name>
		<image>./00Image/Shadow of the Colossus (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Shadow of the Colossus (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Shadow of the Colossus (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Shadow of the Colossus (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The game focuses on a young man named Wander who must travel across a vast expanse on horseback and defeat sixteen beings, simply known as colossi, to restore the life of a girl. The game is unusual within the action-adventure genre in that there are no towns or dungeons to explore, no characters with which to interact, and no enemies to defeat other than the colossi. Shadow of the Colossus has been described as a puzzle game, as each colossus' weakness must be identified and exploited before it can be defeated.</desc>
		<releasedate>20051018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Team Ico, Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Simpsons, The - Hit & Run (USA).iso</path>
		<name>The Simpsons - Hit & Run</name>
		<image>./00Image/Simpsons, The - Hit & Run (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Simpsons, The - Hit & Run (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Simpsons, The - Hit & Run (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Simpsons, The - Hit & Run (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The Simpsons: Hit &amp; Run is a 2003 action-adventure game developed by Radical Entertainment and published by Vivendi Universal Games. It is based on the American animated sitcom The Simpsons, and is the twenty-second installment in the Simpsons series of video games.

The game follows the Simpson family and their friend Apu Nahasapeemapetilon, who witness many strange incidents that occur in Springfield; security cameras, mysterious vans, crop circles, and a "new and improved" flavor of the popular soft drink Buzz Cola that causes insanity. Taking matters into their own hands, they discover numerous shocking secrets, and soon realize these incidents are part of a larger alien conspiracy, caused by Kang and Kodos. The gameplay largely focuses on exploration and missions; players often race enemies and interact with supporting characters on timed quests. The game also features many elements found in role-playing games, such as explorable worlds and side tasks.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Radical Entertainment Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sierra</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sly 2 - Band of Thieves</name>
		<image>./00Image/Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Sly 2 - Band of Thieves (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Thief and raccoon Sly Cooper returns in a new cel-shaded platforming adventure wherein he forms a band of thieves with Bentley the turtle and Murray the purple, hippo-like creature, which each have their own role within the game.

Sly is the fastest, most agile member of the band of thieves and still is the character you play with the most. But certain missions require the special abilities of Bentley, who is smart and can drop bombs, as well shoot enemies from a distance. Other missions require the muscles of Murray, who can lift nearly everything, including enemies.

The main goal of the game is the retrieval of a number of clockwork pieces from different locations around the world. Each theft has to be prepared with a number of sub-missions which have to be completed before the 'real thing' can begin.</desc>
		<releasedate>20041028T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus</name>
		<image>./00Image/Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Sly Cooper and the Thievius Raccoonus (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Sly Cooper is the latest in a long line of master thieves. When he was a kit, a gang called the Fiendish Five killed his family and divided up their book on the art of thieving: the Thievius Raccoonus. Sly must defeat all the members of the gang to recover the book while evading Carmelita Fox, a police officer chasing him around the world to apprehend him.

This game is divided into five worlds, each themed around a particular part of the world and the villain headquartered there. Most worlds are structured as a central hub with entrances to numerous individual levels. Each of the levels has a primary goals which earns you a key. You must collect all the keys in the world to fight the world's boss.

Many of the levels have a platformer structure. The objective of these worlds is to reach the location of the key. There are substantial stealth elements here as you must dodge searchlights and trips lasers which set off alarms and avoid alerting guards. In addition to the main objective, there are clue bottles to find. Finding all the clues in a level allows you to open a safe with a page from the Thievius Raccoonus which grants a new ability of some sort. After getting this, there is also a master thief sprint where you must get from the start of a level to the exit within a time limit.

There are also mini-game levels which could be kart-style racing, several varieties of shooter or assorted other tasks, such as collecting objects before your enemies do.

Boss fights also run to several styles, ranging from platforming, to more straightforward combat to puzzles to rhythm to shooter.

All artwork is done in a cel-shaded style and dialogue is fully voiced</desc>
		<releasedate>20030117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform, Stealth</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spider-Man 3 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Spider-Man 3</name>
		<image>./00Image/Spider-Man 3 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Spider-Man 3 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Spider-Man 3 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Spider-Man 3 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The game's plot expands on the film by including additional characters and elements from the Spider-Man comics and the Marvel Universe. Depending on the platform, different villains from the comics are featured, but all versions of the game feature the film's main villains: Venom, New Goblin, and Sandman.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070504T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Vicarious Visions</developer>
		<publisher>EA Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA).iso</path>
		<name>SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom</name>
		<image>./00Image/SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/SpongeBob SquarePants - Battle for Bikini Bottom (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>SpongeBob SquarePants: Battle for Bikini Bottom is a 2003 video game based on the animated series of the same name. Developed by Heavy Iron Studios, AWE Games and Vicarious Visions and published by THQ. The game was released for the PlayStation 2, Game Boy Advance, Xbox,and Nintendo GameCube consoles as well as for Microsoft Windows. The player attempts to defend Bikini Bottom from an invasion of robots created by Plankton with a machine called the Duplicatotron 3000. The playable characters are SpongeBob, Patrick, and Sandy. The game was released on October 31, 2003 in North America and in Europe on November 28, 2003.</desc>
		<releasedate>20031031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Heavy Iron Studios</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro - A Hero's Tail (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Spyro - A Hero's Tail</name>
		<image>./00Image/Spyro - A Hero's Tail (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Spyro - A Hero's Tail (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Spyro - A Hero's Tail (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Spyro - A Hero's Tail (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Spyro: A Hero's Tail is a 3D platformer in which the player controls a purple dragon named Spyro, as well as five other playable characters.

Spyro and his friends must eliminate the evil Red Dragon by defeating his henchmen and finding the dark gems that are draining the light from the land. Besides the action, the game also features puzzle-solving elements.</desc>
		<releasedate>20041102T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Eurocom</developer>
		<publisher>Vivendi Games</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players></players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken 5 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Tekken 5</name>
		<image>./00Image/Tekken 5 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tekken 5 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tekken 5 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tekken 5 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Loved across the world for its amazing characters, explosive graphics and lightning-fast gameplay, Tekken 5 promises to deliver the next generation of blistered fingers and bleary eyes as it brings players the ultimate, most visually stunning fighting experience ever seen in a Tekken game.

Tekken 5 brings back the popular cast of characters from the previous games along with three new characters for a total of 20 default characters to start, with even more to unlock as you progress in the game. The game allows players to use fight money to customize their character with various accessories such as hats, glasses and an assortment of different costumes. Each of the new characters is equipped with a variety of deadly techniques, and the returning characters have been updated with new moves and combos. New to Tekken 5 is a bonus action adventure game that unfolds a side story to the action-packed fighting sequences.

After the completion of The King of Iron Fist Tournament 4, a fierce battle between father and son unfolded at Mishima Zaibatsu headquarters. Jin emerges as the victor in this battle and continues to defeat Heihachi, his grandfather - but spares both Kazuya and Heihachi's lives in honour of his mother who loved peace. Soon after Jin's departure, a swarm of Jacks arrive at Honmaru and begin to attack Heihachi and Kazuya - and in order to escape, Kazuya thrusts Heihachi into the swarm of Jacks. A great explosion destroys Honmaru, and a man watching from afar reports, "Heihachi Mishima is dead." While many presume the death of Heihachi Mishima will end the reign of Mishima Zaibatsu, an announcement is made for the fifth King of Iron Fist Tournament, with an unknown replacement to Heihachi leading the organization. The fight begins once again.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3</name>
		<image>./00Image/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 3 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>This game saw the introduction of the revert, a trick that enabled vert combos to be tied together with a manual, by tapping a button when landing in a quarterpipe. This allowed for much longer combos than in the previous two games, where landing in a quarterpipe would finish a combo. The game also added hidden combos. These were variations on standard tricks that could be performed as grab, flip, lip, or grind tricks. For example, double-tapping the kickflip button would, naturally, make the character perform a double kickflip.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (Europe, Australia).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4</name>
		<image>./00Image/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (Europe, Australia)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (Europe, Australia)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (Europe, Australia)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tony Hawk's Pro Skater 4 (Europe, Australia)</cartridge>
		<desc>Drop into the ultimate challenge. In the next chapter in the Tony Hawk series, pros challenge you to make your mark in huge free-roaming levels, taking on 190 progressively harder goals with no time limits to hold you back. Decide when you're ready to take on your Pro Challenge and move into the pro ranks, where it's a whole new game. Build your skills, perform all-new tricks, play up to eight players online, and show that you've got what it takes to go Pro.</desc>
		<releasedate>20021023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Tony Hawk's Underground 2</name>
		<image>./00Image/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tony Hawk's Underground 2 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The gameplay in Tony Hawk's Underground 2 is similar to that of previous Tony Hawk games: the player skates around in a 3D environment modeled after various cities and attempts to complete various goals. Most goals involve skating on or over various objects or performing combos. Scores are calculated by adding the sum of the point value of each trick strung together in a combo and then multiplying by the number of tricks in the combo</desc>
		<releasedate>20041004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Neversoft Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Unreal Tournament (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Unreal Tournament</name>
		<image>./00Image/Unreal Tournament (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Unreal Tournament (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Unreal Tournament (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Unreal Tournament (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>From the creators of Unreal comes Unreal Tournament, a competition that tests your reflexes and competitive spirit in deadly arenas. Battle 15 of your friends or customizable bots in over 30 different levels, such as pirate ships, waterfronts, speeding trains, and floating castles. Multiplayer modes include Capture the Flag, Assault, Domination, and new Deathmatch variations. With enhanced weapons--including the Impact hammer, which squashes your opponent to mush, and the Redeemer, a rocket-powered nuke--expect the body count to be high.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Epic Games, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Infogrames Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
