<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Aladdin</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Aladdin (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Aladdin (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Aladdin (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>As Aladdin, baffle the guards in the streets of Agrabah. Elude the tempting traps in the Cave of Wonders, and the dangers of the Sultan's Palace. Ride the magic carpet through breathtaking skies. Then challenge the evil Jafar to a duel of swords and magic!</desc>
		<releasedate>19941231T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alex Kidd in Miracle World (USA, Europe).sms</path>
		<name>Alex Kidd in Miracle World</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Alex Kidd in Miracle World (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Alex Kidd in Miracle World (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Alex Kidd in Miracle World (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Journey through the planet Aries to the beautiful City of Radactian - and save it from the evil Janken the Great. This game was considered to be Sega's attempt on Super Mario.

Alex Kidd in Miracle World is the first of several games in the Alex Kidd series, starring a character which would serve as the company's mascot for half a decade before being replaced by Sonic the Hedgehog.</desc>
		<releasedate>19861201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Alex Kidd in Shinobi World (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Alex Kidd in Shinobi World</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Alex Kidd in Shinobi World (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Alex Kidd in Shinobi World (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Alex Kidd in Shinobi World (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>After ten thousand years, the once banished Dark Ninja returns to make another attempt to take over the Miracle World. Someone's definitely got to stop him! Guess who dares to meet the challenge? You! You're Alex Kidd, the prince who knows no fear.

A lovely girl has been kidnapped and her life is at risk! And she's your girlfriend from the planet Shinobi! By holding her hostage, the Dark Ninja plans to realize his fiendish scheme. She must be saved before it's too late!

You need more than courage to be successful. Transform into a fireball and burn up enemies that come at you. Jump up and across towering walls with your amazing wall-climbing skills. Turn into a tornado and twist your way out. And when you encounter the Dark Ninja, think only of winning. Otherwise you'll lose your girl and, worse yet, the Miracle World will be doomed forever!</desc>
		<releasedate>19900801T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br,en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Asterix (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Asterix</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Asterix (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Asterix (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Asterix (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>The Romans, who fail to conquer one final Gaul village, kidnap Getafix, the druid brewing the magic potion that gives all the inhabitants supernatural strength. Vitalstatistix, the village chief, orders Asterix and Obelix to find him, keep him out of Caesar's hands and bring him back at any cost.

Aside from the traditional moves, there are special potions that melt ice, create makeshift bridges or blow up blocks. The game contains many familiar characters and scenery from the comic books.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Deep Duck Trouble Starring Donald Duck (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Uncle Scrooge found a magical necklace on a mysterious island, but the necklace put a curse on him. Now Uncle Scrooge is doomed to float around in the air forever! (Of course Donald always said Scrooge was full of hot air anyway!) To take the curse off Uncle Scrooge, Donald has to take the necklace back to the island. But there's plenty of danger awaiting Donald there. How about lending him a hand?</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aspect Co. Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E Coyote (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E Coyote</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E Coyote (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E Coyote (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Desert Speedtrap Starring Road Runner and Wile E Coyote (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>This is a platform game starring Looney Tunes famous Road Runner(who you control) and nemesis Wile E. Coyote. Road Runner can jump, eat birdseed to replenish life and run, of course! Holding the D-pad down speeds him up. The clock is ticking and if you run out of time a try is lost, collecting stars adds time to the clock

There are various items/powerups and bonus areas

3 difficulty settings, choice to play with or without music and/or sound effects and an option to play the game music while not in game</desc>
		<releasedate>19940516T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Probe Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Fire & Ice.sms</path>
		<name>Fire & Ice</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Fire & Ice</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Fire & Ice</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Fire & Ice</marquee>
		<desc>The background story of Fire &amp; Ice is quick to tell: A coyote (you) runs, throwing ice cubes, through various worlds. In the levels you must jump on platforms and kill your enemies. The enemies (for example, birds and penguins) can be shot with your ice cubes; they become frozen, so you smash them. Sometimes they leave part of a key behind after they're destroyed. The complete key, assembled from all the pieces, opens the door to the next world.

Released in South America</desc>
		<releasedate>19930101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Graftgold Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Tec Toy Indústria de Brinquedos S.A.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Axe Warrior (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Golden Axe Warrior</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Golden Axe Warrior (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Golden Axe Warrior (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Golden Axe Warrior (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Golden Axe Warrior is a 1991 Master System action-adventure video game developed by Sega CS and released by Sega of America in the USA on April 1, 1991.

World peace is at stake! Death Adder, a wicked giant, has stolen the nine crystals from the kingdom of Firewood and has hidden them in nine labyrinths that he has created. These nine magic crystals protected the people from evil – especially from Death Adder's grasp. But now that the crystals are lost, the world is defenseless!

Someone must put an end to the fiend's realm of darkness, death and destruction! Do you have what it takes to bring back peace and happiness? Trek through deep, dark forests and sail across vast, stormy seas. Chop down trees with your Battle Axe and move rocks with your magic spells to find secret caves. When you take on Death Adder's gruesome monsters, think only of winning – or else you won't find the nine crystals. And when you do, you'll find the Golden Axe – the only weapon that can crush Death Adder!</desc>
		<releasedate>19910401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega CS R&amp;D 2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br,en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golvellius - Valley of Doom (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Golvellius - Valley of Doom</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Golvellius - Valley of Doom (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Golvellius - Valley of Doom (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Golvellius - Valley of Doom (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Enter the world of Golvellius. Where demons rule the valley of water...and control the creatures of land, sea and air. Where almost everyone stands against you. There is only one way in...and no way out except victory or death!

It's an adventure that will take you across deserts and mountains, oceans and forests...through eerie graveyards and caves filled with danger and surprise.

Golvellius has a PASSWORD SAVE feature that lets you keep all your possessions. So you never have to start an adventure empty handed!</desc>
		<releasedate>19881201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Compile</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Land of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Journey with Mickey Mouse through spooky castle ruins, dark caverns, an enchanted forest and a toy shop gone crazy! Use your wits and Mickey's magic to evade challenging traps, explore secret passages, and restore peace and happiness to the Land of Illusion!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920925T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>The Lion King</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Based on the blockbuster animated feature film, Disney's The Lion King brings to life the majesty and mystery of Africa through the tale of Simba, a lion cub. Using animators from the Disney studios and music from the movie soundtrack the video game takes you to Pride Rock.

Fight your way through 10 levels as Simba to the ultimate battle with the evil Uncle Scar. Tackle heinous hyenas in the elephants’ graveyard, avoid the wildebeests’ hooves in the side-scrolling version of the movie's stampede scene. Play the bonus levels as Simbas friends in exile, Pumbaa the warthog and Timon the meerkat.

The partnership of Disney Software and Virgin Interactive Entertainment combine with Sega to make this game the new standard in animation and interactive entertainment.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck, The (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>The Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck, The (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck, The (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lucky Dime Caper Starring Donald Duck, The (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Evil Magica De Spell has stolen the Lucky Dimes and has captured Huey, Dewey and Louie! Trek through six treacherous lands with Donald to save his nephews and retrieve the Lucky Dimes!</desc>
		<releasedate>19911220T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Master of Darkness (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Master of Darkness</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Master of Darkness (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Master of Darkness (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Master of Darkness (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>The shadow of Dracula has spread over Victorian England. Make your way through strange and forbidding streets and cavernous warehouses while fighting his army of monsters. Find Dracula, the Master of Darkness, and rescue England from his terrifying grasp.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sims</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ninja Gaiden (Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Ninja Gaiden</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Ninja Gaiden (Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ninja Gaiden (Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ninja Gaiden (Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>The Dragon Ninja village has been massacred! The powerful scroll of the Bushido has been stolen! You are Ryu Hayabusa, last of the Dragon Ninjas, and you must find the Bushido before it can be used to unleash evil across the Earth!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SIMS Co., Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star (USA, Europe).sms</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Phantasy Star (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Phantasy Star (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Phantasy Star (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Phantasy Star is a 1988 Master System role-playing video game developed by Sega R&amp;D2 and released by Sega of America in the USA on November 1, 1988.

The time: Space Century 3240. The place: The Algol Star System. It began when King Lassic turned evil and let hordes of hideous, magical creatures run amok on the three planets. When her brother was killed, Alis vowed to avenge his death and put an end to Lassic forever.

Join her in a journey across time and space to worlds where creatures speak...where magic and science combine to take you on the ultimate video quest.

Phantasy Star is total adventure role playing with towns full of people and shops...16 level dungeons full of traps and treasure...three companions who will help you if you find them and some of the most awesome graphics ever put in a video game.</desc>
		<releasedate>19881101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Psycho Fox (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Psycho Fox</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Psycho Fox (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Psycho Fox (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Psycho Fox (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Psycho Fox is a 1989 Master System side-scrolling platformer video game developed by VIC Tokai (co-developed by Aicom) and released by Sega of America in the USA on June 1, 1989.

Psycho Fox must get to the right hand side of the level. However, there are many enemies in the way. He can use a Shinto stick to change into characters/animals like a hippopotamus, a monkey or a tiger, each of which has its own special ability. The hippopotamus is slow and cannot jump very high, but can punch through special destructible blocks in the game world. The monkey can jump higher than the other creatures and the tiger can run faster. Psycho also has an ally named Birdfly, who can be used as armor or as a boomerang. If Psycho is hit while carrying Birdfly, Birdfly goes away and the player does not lose a life.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aicom, Vic Tokai</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br,en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Sonic The Hedgehog</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog is a 1991 Master System side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Ancient and released by Sega of America in the USA on October 25, 1991.

Bust the video game speed barrier wide open with Sonic The Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the Super Sonic Spin Attack. Plummet down tunnels and spin through space. Bounce around 'til you're dizzy in a pinball machine. You've never seen anything like it!</desc>
		<releasedate>19911025T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ancient</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>br,en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Voyage - A Sorceress' Vacation.sms</path>
		<name>Voyage - A Sorceress' Vacation</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Voyage - A Sorceress' Vacation</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Voyage - A Sorceress' Vacation</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Voyage - A Sorceress' Vacation</marquee>
		<desc>"KERPLOSHH!" AND LIKE THAT YOUR CRUISE ENDED ON THE SHORE OF A STRANGE ISLAND. CERTAINLY, NOT THE ONE WITH THE 6.5 STAR SPA RESORT YOU WERE LOOKING FORWARD TO ALL YEAR LONG. WELL, THE RESCUE TEAM IS PROBABLY ALREADY ON ITS WAY… OR IS IT?

Completely new levels with a bunch of different styles, more than a dozen new music tracks and even more sound effects, many new features and a few surprises is what we put into this hack, making it a completely different game than Alex Kidd in Miracle World. This is what began its life as a competition entry named “Ma Kai Quest”. Get ready to help our heroine to make her vacation enjoyable in the end and complete all 17 levels. But will completing them be enough to succeed?</desc>
		<releasedate>20211118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SNAGS</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wonder Boy (USA, Europe, Brazil).sms</path>
		<name>Wonder Boy</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Wonder Boy (USA, Europe, Brazil)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Wonder Boy (USA, Europe, Brazil)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Wonder Boy (USA, Europe, Brazil)</marquee>
		<desc>Have you ever wondered what it would be like to set out all alone through the deepest of deep dark forests? To live off the fruit of the land? And fend for yourself against nature's nasty woodland creatures? Have you ever wondered how you'd cope in the middle of a burning desert? With nothing but a skateboard and a glass of milk to see you through? Well now you have to. Because Tanya, the love of your life, has been kidnapped and taken to the other side of the planet. You've got to get her back. As soon as possible. Besides, she'd never forgive you if you didn't risk your life for her.</desc>
		<releasedate>19870601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
