<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>3 Ninjas Kick Back</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/3 Ninjas Kick Back (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>You first saw Rocky, Colt and Tum Tum on the silver screen when their martial arts skills and extreme exploits saved the honor of Grandfather Mori and defeated an evil arms dealer.  Now, it’s up to you!  In this action-packed adventure, you become any one of the 3 Ninjas.  And that’s when the fun begins.  Wild animals and even wilder ninjas attack!  A trio of spaced-out heavy metal rockers join forces with the evil Koga in an all-out effort to do you dirty.  But if you rescue Grandfather Mori and his ceremonial dagger, you’ll have the last laugh… and unlock a secret room filled with more gold than Fort Knox!</desc>
		<releasedate>19940619T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Malibu Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Imagesoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Addams Family, The (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>The Addams Family</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Addams Family, The (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Addams Family, The (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Addams Family, The (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Creepy, Kooky, Ooky, Spooky.

THE ADDAMS FAMILY has been evicted! To save their home from Tully Alford, the family attorney, who is after the family fortune - Morticia, Lurch, Granny, Pugsley and Wednesday have gone to the house to reason with him. But when Gomez arrives, his family is missing! As Gomez, you must save your loved ones, your home and your loads of wealth. You'll have to watch out for scary obstacles like falling spikes, frightening monsters and ghosts, and you'll need to look for clues as you search for your family. Get a move on... 'cause you're gonna make a call on THE ADDAMS FAMILY!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Enigma Variations Ltd., Ocean Software Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Ocean Software Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Aero the Acro-Bat 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Aero the Acro-Bat 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>In the sequel to Aero the Acro-Bat you have to defeat evil industrialist Edgar Ektor once again. He is back and again with bad ideas, so you - in the role of Aero - have to find and destroy him before he carries out his diabolical "Plan B". Like in the last installment, you have to jump, escape lethal obstacles and progress in time. This game features more moves for Aero, more mechanisms to use and more items to collect.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Aladdin</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Aladdin (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Aladdin (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Aladdin (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Discover a Whole New World of Adventure... For years, Jafar, the Sultan's evil advisor has sought a magic treasure - a single lamp that holds the key to the greatest power in the world. With this goal in sight, Jafar learns that only one person in the world can claim the magic lamp from the dreaded Cave of Wonders - one whose rags hide a heart that is pure - a diamond in the rough! Join Aladdin and his pet monkey Abu, as they race through the marketplace toward their date with destiny. Watch as Jafar tricks our hero and his friend into retrieving the lamp from the dangerous Cave of Wonders. But Aladdin and Abu outwit Jafar, releasing the power of a wacky blue Genie! Now Aladdin will have the chance to spoil Jafar's devious plans and win the hand of the beautiful princess Jasmine. But it will take more than magic to make his wishes come true...</desc>
		<releasedate>19931123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./A Plumber For All Seasons.sfc</path>
		<name>A Plumber For All Seasons</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/A Plumber For All Seasons</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/A Plumber For All Seasons</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/A Plumber For All Seasons</marquee>
		<desc>A Plumber For All Seasons is a hack I've worked on for a long time. Each world represents a different season — there's a Spring world, a Summer world, a Fall world, and a Winter world. (And some more!) Almost all the graphics are custom and hand-made.</desc>
		<releasedate>20211211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>wye</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker's High Rule Tail.sfc</path>
		<name>Conker's High Rule Tail</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Conker's High Rule Tail</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Conker's High Rule Tail</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Conker's High Rule Tail</marquee>
		<desc>Initially built as a spiritual sequel to Parallel Worlds, this project has evolved so much overtime that eventually it became an unofficial sequel to an M Rated game that was released late in the Nintendo 64 lifespan, none other than Conker’s Bad Fur Day!

Including all the same crude humor found in that Conker game and the many references to movies and games we’ve come to love. For obvious reasons, it is also rated "AO for Adults Only"!</desc>
		<releasedate>20211124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SePH</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Demon's Crest (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Demon's Crest</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Demon's Crest (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Demon's Crest (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Demon's Crest (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The demon realm is peaceful until six wondrous stones fall from the sky. Each stone represents a portion of the Demon's Crest. When united, the stones of the Demon's Crest bring the user ultimate power over demons and humans.
These stones were so highly sought that clvil war broke out in the realm. The fight led to much bloodshed until one gargoyle emerged victorious: the red demon known as Firebrand.
After Firebrand‘s final battle, his evil nemesis Phalanx ambushed Firebrand and stole the stones. Now Firebrand must recover the stones and unlte the power of the Demon's Crest before both realms fall into the hands of the sinister Phalanx!

*Morph into 6 different forms to explore new areas when you find parts of the Demon‘s Crest
*Incredible Mode 7 effects as Firebrand flies high above
the demon realm, overlooking 7 intense levels
*25 items hidden in the realm. with different endings based on how many items you find
*For one player</desc>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Country 2 - Diddy's Kong Quest (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Country 2: Diddy's Kong Quest is a 1995 SNES side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Rare and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on November 20, 1995.

O.K. KID, WIPE THAT DROOL OFF YOUR CHIN AND LISTEN UP IF YOU REALLY WANT TO LEARN SOMETHING ABOUT THIS GAME. Sure, it's got NEWFANGLED COMPUTER GRAPHICS and what Diddy calls stereo sound that rocks heavily and with little resistance! BUT, the game play Well, they FINALLY added some proper challenge to the game - a snap for me of course. AND THE STORY You sure ask a lot of questions, kid! Kaptain K. Rool and his cruelest cut-throat Kremlings have kidnapped that flea-bitten ape Donkey Kong. I figured I'd rescue him when the little pip-squeak DIDDY pops up along with his girlfriend, and they head off fixin' to prove themselves heroes or something. Come to think of it, I haven't laid eyes on those two for quite a while. I just may have to help them out after all!

*PLAY AS DIDDY OR DIXIE KONG, EACH WITH UNIQUE ABILITIES!
*EIGHT EXCITING WORLDS WITH ALL-NEW LEVELS AND KREMLINGS!
*BRAND NEW KONG FAMILY MEMBERS AND FRIENDS!
*TONS OF NEW MOVES AND SPECIAL ABILITIES!
*MORE SECRETS AND CHALLENGES THAN DONKEY KONG COUNTRY!</desc>
		<releasedate>19951120T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble!</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Country 3 - Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Country 3: Dixie Kong's Double Trouble! is a 1996 SNES side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Rare and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on November 18, 1996.

Monkey Mayhem Lives On!

Kiddy Kong is a portly primate toddler with incredible power and agility! He teams up with Dixie Kong to stop the ever-present army of Kremlings. The game play and ACM graphics just keep getting better in this visually stunning installment in one of the most popular video game series of all time!

Combining their unique abilities as they throw each other into action, Dixie Kong and Kiddy Kong set off to rescue Diddy Kong and Donkey Kong. Collect tons of treasure, grab billions of bananas and find more secret stuff than you've ever seen (or not seen) as you set off on the greatest DKC adventure yet! The final showdown with KAOS takes place in a cliff-top laboratory at the End of the World. It could get seriously ugly. Monkey mayhem lives on in this exotic island adventure!</desc>
		<releasedate>19961118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Country (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Donkey Kong Country is a 1994 SNES side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Rare and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on November 21, 1994.

Madness and Mayhem in this 3D Gorilla Thriller!

Donkey Kong is back with a new sidekick, Diddy Kong, in a crazy island adventure! Challenged by the crazed tribe of reptilian Kremlings, they endeavor to get back their stolen banana horde! Armed with lightning-quick moves, chest-pounding muscle and awesome aerial acrobatics, our duo is ready to face their cunning adversaries. With the help of Donkey Kong's quirky family and his wild animal mounts, they squabble and scamper their way through the unending monkey mayhem!</desc>
		<releasedate>19941121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>F-Zero</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/F-Zero (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/F-Zero (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/F-Zero (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>F-Zero is a 1991 SNES racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on August 23, 1991.

F-Zero is set in the year 2560, when humanity's multiple encounters with alien life forms had resulted in the expansion of Earth's social framework. This led to commercial, technological and cultural interchanges between planets. The multi-billionaires who earned their wealth through intergalactic trade were mainly satisfied with their lifestyles, although most coveted more entertainment in their lives. This resulted in a new entertainment based on the Formula One races to be founded with vehicles that could hover one foot above the track. These Grand Prix races were soon named "F-Zero" after a rise in popularity of the races. The game introduced the first set of F-Zero racers: Captain Falcon, Dr. Stewart, Pico, and Samurai Goroh.</desc>
		<releasedate>19910823T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Kirby Super Star (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Kirby Super Star</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Kirby Super Star (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Kirby Super Star (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Kirby Super Star (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Kirby Super Star is a 1996 SNES side-scrolling platformer video game developed by HAL Laboratory and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on September 20, 1996.

Power up for EIGHT action-packed battles and adventures!
Dream Land is under siege again! Our hero, Kirby, returns to instigate a rescue. King Dedede is snatching up Dream Land's food supply, but he's not the only one! Dyna Blade, Meta Knight and a slew of other evil baddies are on the loose and wreaking havoc throughout the land.

Use any of Kirby's amazing powers to create a "helper" to assist you in battle. Or have a friend join you for some two-player action by taking control of Kirby's helper. Help Kirby work through EIGHT challenging games filled with action and adventure. Enter the fray in Spring Breeze, enter a foot race against King Dedede in Gourmet Race and tackle a winged warrior in Dyna Blade. Hone your reaction skills in Megaton Punch and Samurai Kirby, then battle your way through the Great Cave Offensive, Revenge of Meta Knight and Milky Way Wishes. Each game is different AND some extra-special surprises are in store for you!

*Includes EIGHT action-packed games and special surprises!
*Two-player action is possible when you activate Kirby's "helper" feature!
*Huge 32-meg game provides excellent entertainment value for Kirby fans of all ages!
*Battery back-up saves your progress and best scores!</desc>
		<releasedate>19960920T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - A Link to the Past</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - A Link to the Past (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Play as Link, journey through the kingdom of Hyrule, conquer dungeons, and face off against the evil Ganon in a legendary adventure to rescue Princess Zelda and the Seven Sages.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920413T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The [Proto] (Early Prototype).sfc</path>
		<name>The Lion King [Proto]</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The [Proto] (Early Prototype)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The [Proto] (Early Prototype)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The [Proto] (Early Prototype)</marquee>
		<desc>A very early prototype of The Lion King was found and dumped by Z in 2015. Interestingly, the Master System and Game Gear versions of the game are based on this prototype.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Unreleased</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Adventure, Prototype</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>The Lion King</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Experience Simba's journey from cub to king in Disney’s The Lion King. Navigate iconic locations from the movie, face off against hyenas, and defeat Scar to fulfill your destiny.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Virgin Interactive Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lord of the Rings, The - Volume 1 (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>The Lord of the Rings - Volume 1</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lord of the Rings, The - Volume 1 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lord of the Rings, The - Volume 1 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lord of the Rings, The - Volume 1 (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Embark on an epic quest in the world of Middle-earth. Play as Frodo, Gandalf, and other characters as you battle enemies and journey toward Mount Doom in this RPG adaptation of Tolkien’s classic tale.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Interplay Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario is missing! Done Right!.sfc</path>
		<name>Mario is missing! Done Right!</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario is missing! Done Right!</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario is missing! Done Right!</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario is missing! Done Right!</marquee>
		<desc>What if Mario is Missing weren’t a boring edutainment title? This hack intends to be what most players expected Mario is Missing to be: a platformer starring Luigi on a quest to save Mario. The hack contains 7 Worlds and is comparable in difficulty to official Mario games.</desc>
		<releasedate>20170723T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamma V</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Is Missing! (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Mario Is Missing!</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Is Missing! (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Is Missing! (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Is Missing! (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Don't look now, but Bowser's back, and this time he's in your world! But where is that mastermind of reptilian trouble doing his dastardly deeds? And what has he done with Mario? Welcome to Mario is Missing! Take a trek with your travel agent, Luigi, and see the world! Track down troublesome turtles. Figure out where in the world you are, and what on earth happened to Mario. If your grasp of geography is good enough, you'll get the goods, stomp the hoods, and grab Mario out of Bowser's ghastly guest house. A learning adventure that the whole family can share! This is no Koopa-stomping mayhem. It's a fun way to learn about our world!</desc>
		<releasedate>19930601T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Software Creations</developer>
		<publisher>The Software Toolworks, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Mario Kart</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Kart (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Kart (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Kart (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Super Mario Kart is a 1992 SNES racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on September 1, 1992.

The Super Mario Go-Kart Park is open for tons of racing fun!  Hit the track with Mario, Luigi, Yoshi and the Princess.  Get tough and lock fenders with Donkey Kong, Jr. and Bowser.  Even Toad and Koopa Troopa will mix it up in an all-out quest for the Gold Cup!  Race head-to-head with a friend or challenge the computer in great, split-screen, Mode 7 graphics.

Feel like a bit less speed and a lot more strategy?  Take a crack at the Battle Mode!  In four different maze-like courses you’ll use Koopa Shells, Banana Peels, Super Stars and other wacky weapons to burst your opponent's target balloons and triumph!

* 2 games in 1 - Mario Grand Prix and Battle Mode
* 8  Familiar Characters
* 20 Different Tracks
* 3 Different Skill Levels
* Battery-backed memory saves your best times!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920901T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario RPG - Legend of the Seven Stars (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Mario and friends embark on a grand role-playing adventure to defeat the evil Smithy and his minions. Collect stars, battle foes, and team up with unlikely allies to save the Mushroom Kingdom.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960513T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Square</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man X3 (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Mega Man X3</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mega Man X3 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mega Man X3 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mega Man X3 (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Mega Man X3 is a 1995 SNES side-scrolling action platformer video game developed by Capcom and released by Capcom USA in the USA on January 4, 1996.

Mega Man X and his trusty partner Zero have a new force to reckon with. Who or what has caused a riot of Mavericks to break out in the experimental utopia known as Doppler Town?

Named after the scientist reploid, Doppler Town was supposed to be a place where humans and reploids could live in harmony. After discovering a virus that was turning reploids to Mavericks, Doppler's anti-virus was a big success. But Doppler itself became infected with the virus and assembled a team to take out the Maverick Hunter Units. The Doppler Effect is about to unfold, with Mega Man X and Zero the only cure for the deadly virus!</desc>
		<releasedate>19960104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Minakuchi Engineering</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom USA, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./New Super Mario Land (J).sfc</path>
		<name>New Super Mario Land</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/New Super Mario Land (J)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/New Super Mario Land (J)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/New Super Mario Land (J)</marquee>
		<desc>New Super Mario Land is a homebrew release that re-imagines Super Mario Land, the iconic Game Boy title, on the Super Nintendo.
It combines the Game Boy original with New Super Mario Bros style graphics and adds gameplay features such as a four player simultaneous multiplayer mode.
It was developed in secret by a mystery coder and 30 custom cartridges of it were sent out to select people to celebrate the Game Boy's 30th Anniversary.</desc>
		<releasedate>20190421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ChronoMoogle</developer>
		<publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>jp</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shadowrun (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Shadowrun</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Shadowrun (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Shadowrun (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Shadowrun (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Disoriented and confused, you are forced into a race against time, technology and termination. Running in the shadows and cracks between the Megaplexes, survival depends on your wits, your weapons and your wayward companions. Plunge into the dark side of the future, where technology and magic become one, where devolution and destruction are a way of life. Plunge into Shadowrun.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930501T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Beam Software</developer>
		<publisher>Data East Corporation</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Star Fox</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Fox (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Fox (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Fox (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Star Fox, known as Starwing in the PAL regions, is a 3D rail shooter video game developed by Nintendo and Argonaut Software for the Super Nintendo Entertainment System. The first game in the Star Fox series, the story follows Fox McCloud and the rest of the Star Fox team defending their homeworld of Corneria against the invading forces of Andross.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Games, Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario All-Stars (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Mario All-Stars</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario All-Stars (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario All-Stars (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario All-Stars (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Super Mario All-Stars is a 1993 SNES side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on August 11, 1993.

Revisit the magic and fun of the classic Super Mario Bros. series on your Super NES! All the great Super Mario Bros. games for the NES have been powered up with 16-bit graphics and sound and collected on one super Game Pak. As an added bonus, the previously unreleased “Lost Levels” are included.  These super challenging courses have never been available in this country until now!

* Four great games in one Game Pak!
* Battery backed memory saves up to 4 players’ progress through every game!
* Play alone or 2 players can alternate play!
* New 16-bit graphics, sound, and other surprises!</desc>
		<releasedate>19930811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario World 2 - Yoshi's Island (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Yoshi embarks on an adventure to reunite Baby Mario with his brother, Baby Luigi, through colorful worlds, challenging puzzles, and memorable enemies in this classic platforming prequel.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951004T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario World (USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Mario World</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario World (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario World (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario World (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Join Mario on his quest to rescue Princess Toadstool from Bowser across the dinosaur-themed world of Super Mario World. With Yoshi at his side, Mario faces new challenges, power-ups, and secrets.</desc>
		<releasedate>19900813T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Metroid (Japan, USA).sfc</path>
		<name>Super Metroid</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Metroid (Japan, USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Metroid (Japan, USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Metroid (Japan, USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Super Metroid is a 1994 SNES side-scrolling metroidvania platformer video game developed by Nintendo R&amp;D1 (co-developed by Intelligent Systems) and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on April 18, 1994.

Take on a legion of Space Pirates and a new Metroid force as you forge into the covert underworld of Planet Zebes!  It’s up to you and Samus to recapture the long-surviving Metroid hatchling before evil hands unleash its energy.

An army of ominous creatures are poised for battle at every turn of Zebes’ twisted, threatening passageways… including the menacing Ridley and the great lizard Kraid.  Knock down enemies with a killer somersault and swing on an electric beam through narrow passageways!  They’re no match for you and Samus… but wait!  It seems the Mother Brain has returned…</desc>
		<releasedate>19940418T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems Co., Ltd., Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en,jp</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Classic Kong (Shiru).smc</path>
		<name>Classic Kong</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Classic Kong (Shiru)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Classic Kong (Shiru)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Classic Kong (Shiru)</marquee>
		<desc>We are proud announce the release of Classic Kong, a faithful recreation of a classic title for the SNES. Yes, an actual new SNES ROM. It’s free of copy-protection and free of charge, and we’ve even released the source code for you hobbyist types. Special thanks to Shiru for his hard work as lead developer.

Update: Second release! Because of the great response and requests for more content we’ve now added the pie factory level plus some more extras.</desc>
		<releasedate>20120918T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>SuperGNES</developer>
		<publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Country 4 - The Kremling's Revenge.smc</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Country 4 - The Kremling's Revenge</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 4 - The Kremling's Revenge</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Country 4 - The Kremling's Revenge</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Country 4 - The Kremling's Revenge</marquee>
		<desc>A fan-made continuation of the Donkey Kong Country series, where Donkey Kong faces the Kremlings once again. Set across new jungle terrains and underwater levels, this game brings back DKC’s signature gameplay with added challenges and secrets.</desc>
		<releasedate>20120114T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Preposterify</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
