<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Carmageddon (Europe).m3u</path>
		<name>Carmageddon</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Carmageddon (Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Carmageddon (Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Carmageddon (Europe)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Carmageddon (Europe)</cart>
		<desc>In Carmageddon, the player races a vehicle against a number of other computer controlled competitors in various settings, including city, mine and industrial areas. The player has a certain amount of time to complete each race, but more time may be gained by collecting bonuses, damaging the competitors' cars or by running over pedestrians.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Stainless Games Ltd</developer>
		<publisher>SCi Games Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Symphony of the Night</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Castlevania - Symphony of the Night (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Castlevania: Symphony of the Night is a 1997 PlayStation side-scrolling horror metroidvania action role-playing platformer video game developed by Konami Computer Entertainment Tokyo and released by Konami Inc. in the USA on October 3, 1997.

Five years ago, Richter Belmont, the latest in the Belmont lineage and the one destined to be a Vampire Hunter, defeated Dracula in a brutal battle which nearly cost him the love of his life, Annette, and her sister, Maria. Now, Richter has suddenly vanished, Castlevania has mysteriously reappeared, and Maria, now a young woman, sets off to find Richter. Alucard, the son of Dracula, is awakened from his eternal slumber after this large shift in power, and enters into Castlevania to find some answers and perhaps destroy the castle once again.

Symphony of the Night is a direct sequel to Dracula X: Rondo of Blood. The game is set in a castle which you can explore freely with many different paths, although often items in certain areas need to be found that will allow passage to others. The action-based gameplay incorporates now strong RPG elements. The hero receives experience points for defeating enemies, gains levels and becomes more powerful. There is also money to be found in the game, and various accessories to buy. In a separate screen, players need to equip attack weapons, shields and other items. Magic plays an important role, as well as secondary weapons and a large amount of "special moves" that are executed similar to advanced one-on-one fighting games.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971003T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Tokyo</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Platform, Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chrono Cross (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Chrono Cross</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Chrono Cross (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Chrono Cross (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Chrono Cross (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Chrono Cross (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Chrono Cross features standard RPG gameplay with some differences. Players advance the game by controlling the protagonist Serge through the game's world, primarily by foot and boat. Navigation between areas is conducted via an overworld map, much like Chrono Trigger's, depicting the landscape from a scaled down overhead view. Around the island world are villages, outdoor areas, and dungeons, through which the player moves in three dimensions. Locations such as cities and forests are represented by more realistically scaled field maps, in which players can converse with locals to procure items and services, solve puzzles and challenges, or encounter enemies. Like Chrono Trigger, the game features no random encounters; enemies are openly visible on field maps or lie in wait to ambush the party</desc>
		<releasedate>19991118T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Crash Bandicoot 2 - Cortex Strikes Back (USA)</cart>
		<desc>The evil Dr. Neo Cortex is back with a vengeance... this time... to save the world? And he's asking for help from his arch-nemesis, Crash Bandicoot? Or is it just some conniving plan to lure Crash into a deadly trap for his own evil bidding? Find out as Crash takes on a whole new adventure that's out of this world!</desc>
		<releasedate>19971218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Crash Bandicoot (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Crash Bandicoot (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Crash Bandicoot is a 1996 PlayStation third-person platformer video game developed by Naughty Dog and released by Sony Computer Entertainment America, under license by Universal Interactive Studios, in the USA on September 9, 1996.

Crash Bandicoot, a heroic, agile and mutated marsupial who must save his girlfriend Tawna. The main antagonist is Doctor Neo Cortex, a mad scientist who was often ridiculed by the scientific community for his outlandish (but nearly workable) theories and is now motivated to prove his tormentors wrong by creating a mutated army of beasts to conquer the world. Cortex's henchman is Doctor Nitrus Brio, the insecure creator of the Evolvo-Ray. Crash's love interest is Tawna, a female bandicoot about to undergo experimentation by the Doctors. Helping Crash in his journey is an ancient witch doctor spirit named Aku Aku, who has scattered masks of himself throughout the islands to grant Crash special powers. The boss characters of the game include Papu Papu, the obese and short-tempered chief of the native village; Ripper Roo, a demented kangaroo with razor-sharp toenails; Koala Kong, a muscular but unintelligent koala; and Pinstripe Potoroo, the tommy gun-wielding bodyguard of Doctor Cortex.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog Software</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive Inc., Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Crash Bandicoot - Warped</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Crash Bandicoot - Warped (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Ga mee met Crash Bandicoot in  een race tegen de tijd om de wereld te redden. Met volledig nieuxe animaties, een boel nieuwe voertuigen en een te gekke verzameling karakters!

Mit neu gestalteten Animationen, einer Riesenauswahl an Fortbewegungsmitteln und einer abgedrehten Besetzung - Begeben Sie sich mit Crash Bandicoot aud eine atemberaubende Zeitreise, um die Welt zu retten!

Con le animazioni tutte nuove e i tantissimi nuovi veicoli, un folle cast di personnaggi si unisce a Crash Bandicoot in una gara nel tempo per salvare il destino dell'intero universo.

Plongés dans des décors inédits et aux commandes de tout nouveaux véhicules, des personnages détraqués rejoignent Crash Bandicoot dans une course à travers le temps pour sauver le monde!</desc>
		<releasedate>19981201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Naughty Dog Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Digimon World (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Digimon World</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Digimon World (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Digimon World (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Digimon World (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Digimon World (USA)</cart>
		<desc>The PlayStation's answer to the Pokémon series phenomenon from Nintendo, Digimon World lets you raise customized Digimon monsters, training them for battle against other Digimon found in Digimon World. Most Digimon originally called File Island home, but for some unknown reason over time they lost the ability to speak and now live a nomadic lifestyle.

It is your goal to roam the dangerous countryside with your trained Digimon battling other lost Digimon. A victorious battle permits them to return home to the abandoned File Island. The main one-player mode on Digimon World is where the mysterious story unfolds as you raise your immature Digimon. Digimon are dependant on you for happiness, food, and parental guidance to guide their behavior (similar to the popular Tamagotchi toy).

Digimon mature while "working out" in the training area and as you battle various Digimon in the surrounding areas. Your pet Digimon can compete against friends' Digimon in Battle Mode that provides an arena for head-to-head combat. A loss against a friend can provide plenty of initiative to return to the main mode to strengthen your Digimon, but you'll need one block of free space on the memory card to save your progress.</desc>
		<releasedate>20000523T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Flying Tiger Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Disney's Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Take control of Aladdin and stop Nasira, the evil sister of Jafar (the bad guy from the Disney movie) and rescue the Sultan and Princess Jasmine. Based on the hit Disney movie and the animated TV series of the same name</desc>
		<releasedate>20010315T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Games</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Disney's Donald Duck - Goin' Quackers (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Daisy, reporter sans frontières, se fait enlever par le diabolique magicien Merlock. Donald décide de partir à sa rescousse. Mais son cousin Gontran est aussi parti la sauver, DOnald doit donc se dépêcher! Grâce à une invention géniale de Géo Touveton, Donald pourra être téléporté travers le monde, puis jusqu'au temple de Merlock pour sauver Daisy.
- Donald peut être joyeux, hyperactif, fâché ou fou de rage: à toi de maîtriser ses humeurs pour le rendre le plus efficace possible!
- 4 mondes inédits: le Mont Donald, Donaldville, le manoir de Miss Tick et le temple de Merlock.
- 24 niveaux exclusifs en 3D dont 4 niveaux bonus de poursuites.
- Un bonus supplémentaire pour changer le costume de Donald.
- 4 boss dont l'inédite Bernadette.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001019T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Disney Interactive</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Disney's The Lion King - Simba's Mighty Adventure (USA)</cart>
		<desc>After his father is killed, the young lion prince Simba must travel through the jungle to find his life's path. Eventually, he will return home and claim his rightful place as the Lion King. On his journey, Simba must avoid such dangers of the jungles and plains as wildebeests and rhinos. When he encounters these enemies as a cub, his roar does little to scare them off. However, maturing into a majestic lion deepens his voice and makes the growl useful as a weapon. As he explores the nine levels, Simba will be able to collect a wide variety of items that will open several bonuses that include puzzles, mini-games, and movies. While the film was animated in 2D, Simba and his world are rendered in three dimensions, and the plot unfolds in cinematic sequences between each level. You've got to help Simba take his rightful place in DISNEY'S THE LION KING: Simba's Mighty Adventure.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Paradox Development</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Disney's The Little Mermaid II (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Disney's The Little Mermaid II</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Disney's The Little Mermaid II (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Disney's The Little Mermaid II (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Disney's The Little Mermaid II (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Disney's The Little Mermaid II (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Fourteen years have passed since Ariel first defeated Ursula, married Prince Eric and got herself a pair of legs. Now her daughter, Melody, has decided to go against her mother's wishes to search the ocean for the city of Atlantis. Children begin the adventure as Ariel, reliving the events of the first movie. Once they defeat Ursula, kids change over to Melody and start their search for Atlantis. Disney did an excellent job making the controls simple enough for even young children to use. The goals and obstacles are also fairly simple- collect coins and pearls, for example. Even more impressive are the spoken instructions that accompany the on-screen text. These features combine to make the game accessible to a younger age range.</desc>
		<releasedate>20020603T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>THQ</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Final Fantasy VII (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Final Fantasy VII</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Final Fantasy VII (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Final Fantasy VII (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Final Fantasy VII (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Final Fantasy VII (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Final Fantasy VII is a 1997 PlayStation role-playing video game developed by Square and released by Sony Computer Entertainment America in the USA on September 7, 1997.

Set in a dystopian world, Final Fantasy VII's story centers on mercenary Cloud Strife who joins with several others to stop the megacorporation Shinra, which is draining the life of the planet to use as an energy source. As the story progresses, the situation escalates and Cloud and his allies face Sephiroth, the game's main antagonist.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970907T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Gex 3 - Deep Cover Gecko (USA)</cart>
		<desc>When Gex is watching TV one day, he discovers that Rez has kidnapped Agent Xtra (the agent from Gex: Enter the Gecko's backstory), head of the TV Terrorist Defense Unit, to get to him. He teleports to the batcave-like lair he has in the Media Dimension, and begins another adventure. Each level parodies a certain aspect of television culture (here the levels exist as stand-alone channels). Gex enters each level through a television set. He must collect remote controls to advance to the next level in order to complete his mission and rescue Xtra.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gex - Enter the Gecko (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Gex - Enter the Gecko</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Gex - Enter the Gecko (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Gex - Enter the Gecko (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Gex - Enter the Gecko (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Gex - Enter the Gecko (USA)</cart>
		<desc>"Is it just me, or am I engulfed in flames?" is one of the many one-liners uttered by Gex, a wise cracking gecko who should check himself into television rehab; he's addicted to it. After saving the Television Realm from the evil Rez in his first adventure, the gecko was ready to kick back, relax, and watch a little television. Little did he know his adventure was just beginning.

One day, two secret agent goons showed up at Gex's doorstep. They inform him that Rez is back and looking for vengeance; the evil monster is planning to destroy the Television Realm once more...and possibly the world. When Gex tells them that he's retired and doesn't care, one of the goons hits the gecko on the head and takes him to a secluded place.

When Gex comes to, the mystery men plead with the gecko to take the cash and help destroy Rez for good...or at least make him disappear. With that incentive (the cash), the wise cracking lizard slips into his special agent suit and plunges headfirst into the Television Realm. Watch out, Rez -- Gex is back!</desc>
		<releasedate>19980224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gex (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Gex</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Gex (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Gex (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Gex (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Gex (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Enter your television to defeat the evil Rez by collecting remotes to open worlds inside your tv. You are a gecko with all the usual platform hero skills such as jump, fire and close range attack, but also suction cups to help you scale walls, a tongue to pick up those tricky to get power-ups and plenty of wise-cracks to keep you amused. Use them all to make your way through TV land searching for the remotes, collecting pickups, power-ups and killing TVs.</desc>
		<releasedate>19951201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Crystal Dynamics, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Grand Theft Auto (USA)</cart>
		<desc>In Grand Theft Auto, the player takes the role of a small-time criminal trying to make it big with the mob. Stealing cars, doing jobs for the gangsters and behaving generally anti-social are the way to success.

The action moves through six levels spread over three different cities, each based on a real US city: Liberty City (based on New York City), San Andreas (based on San Francisco) and Vice City (based on Miami). To finish a level, a certain score must be reached. Stealing cars and crashing into traffic, driving over pedestrians and killing cops all raise the score, but the big points are made through jobs. Answering phones or entering special cars brings mission assignments, from simple "ditch-a-hot-car" jobs to supporting bank robberies or carrying out assassinations. Completing a mission will raise the score substantially and also increase the score multiplier, so that completing the next felony will gain even more points.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited, Visual Sciences Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Take-Two Interactive Software, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone (USA)</cart>
		<desc>J. K. Rowling's immensely popular boy wizard makes his highly anticipated entrance to the realm of video gaming with this third-person 3D action-adventure based on Harry Potter and the Sorcerer's Stone, the first novel in the series. In the role of the prodigious young magician the player begins his first year at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry, joined by familiar characters such as Ron Weasley, Hermione Granger, and even Draco Malfoy.

Harry Potter can explore the grounds at Hogwarts, spend time with Hagrid, and even hop on a broomstick for a quick game of quidditch. However, as in the novel, Harry's special gifts are noticed not only by his instructors but by darker forces, as well, and the player may even come face-to-face with "You-Know-Who" himself before this adventure is over.</desc>
		<releasedate>20011115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Argonaut Games</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Klonoa - Door to Phantomile</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Klonoa - Door to Phantomile (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Explore a magical world of mystery and adventure. Join Klonoa on a fantastic journey in the land of Phantomile, where the mysterious crash of a flying ship starts an epic quest through colorful worlds of thrills and danger.

You're never lost in this 3-D world. Klonoa's "Guided 3-D" construction gives players a vast 3-D world without the aimless and wandering feel of many other 3-D action games.

Beautiful graphics and entertaining puzzles add a whole new level of fun &amp; challenge.

Multiple, forked paths add extra replay value - just remember that shortcuts aren't always what they seem!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Namco</developer>
		<publisher>Namco</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Dragoon, The (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>The Legend of Dragoon</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Dragoon, The (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Dragoon, The (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Dragoon, The (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Legend of Dragoon, The (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Hero, Dart travels home to his village after returning from a failed journey to avenge the deaths of his parents. When he arrives he finds that the village has been destroyed and his childhood sweetheart, Shana, has been captured by a military force loyal to the evil dictator Emperor Doel. As he begins his adventure to free Shana and keep her safe, he discovers that he has inherited the power of the Dragoon, a knight who fought in an ancient battle for the survival of humans. Now, the war is about to begin again and Dart must protect the world and Shana, who plays a mysterious part in the whole affair. On his adventure he will encounter other dragoons, both friends and enemies and together they will battle on to the final fight...</desc>
		<releasedate>20000613T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Mana (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Legend of Mana</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Mana (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Mana (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Mana (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Legend of Mana (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Create Your World
In ancient times, the world was saved from destruction by sealing locations and events within magical artifacts. Now, you have the chance to recreate this world as you desire by discovering artifacts, placing them, and exploring the mysteries inside.

-Construct a unique world map and story by carefully placing artifacts.
-Explore areas in any order, encountering nearly 70 different gameplay scenarios.
-Battle enemies in real-time with special attacks and customizable controls.
-Control every aspect of your new world: raise faithful net monsters, create powerful golems, forge mighty weapons, and refine magical instruments.
-Adventure with a friend by having them import their Legend of Mana character from a MEMORY CARD, or take control of an NPC .</desc>
		<releasedate>20000607T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Squaresoft</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MediEvil II (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>MediEvil II</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/MediEvil II (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/MediEvil II (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/MediEvil II (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/MediEvil II (USA)</cart>
		<desc>In MediEvil 2, Sir Daniel Fortesque has been summoned again 500 years later--in 1888 A.D.--because evil magician Lord Palethorn has found pages from Zarok's spell book. Now Victorian London is overrun by undead, and it's your job, as Dan Fortesque, to fight through several levels and stop Palethorn before he takes over the world.</desc>
		<releasedate>20000421T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Guerrilla Cambridge</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./MediEvil (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>MediEvil</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/MediEvil (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/MediEvil (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/MediEvil (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/MediEvil (USA)</cart>
		<desc>The game starts with a flashback in the 13th century in the fictional English Kingdom of Gallowmere. The game puts the player in control of Sir Daniel Fortesque: the reanimated skeletal remains of a deceased champion knight whom history holds in high esteem, due to his supposed heroics in battle against the evil sorcerer Zarok who, in 1286, had raised an army of demons and set out to take over the kingdom. The legend has it that Fortesque lead the King's army into battle against Zarok's demonic hordes and that Sir Daniel himself killed the sorcerer during the battle - despite having actually been mortally wounded at the outset - cementing his posthumous status as the "Hero of Gallowmere".</desc>
		<releasedate>19981021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Cambridge Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Parasite Eve (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Parasite Eve</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Parasite Eve (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Parasite Eve (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Parasite Eve (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Parasite Eve (USA)</cart>
		<desc>THE CINEMATIC RPG

One of them is a police officer. The other is possessed by an ancient evil threatening all life on Earth. The horrifying bond between them will continue until something dies.
A chilling adventure that could only come from the creators of Final Fantasy VII
An epic sci-fi tale told through stunning 3D rendered sequences
Battle mutant monsters in real-time polygon combat
Customize weapons, armor, and character abilities</desc>
		<releasedate>19980909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Squaresoft</developer>
		<publisher>Square EA</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Horror</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage!</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Spyro 2 - Ripto's Rage! (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Spyro 2: Ripto's Rage! is the second game in the Spyro the Dragon series, which started with Spyro the Dragon in 1998. The protagonist of the series, Spyro, is placed in the land of Avalar, rather than the Dragon Worlds, where the previous installment was set. A dinosaur-riding sorcerer, known as Ripto, has invaded the world of Avalar, and is wreaking havoc on its citizens with his magic. The player, as Spyro, must travel through the world of Avalar and undo the damage done by Ripto.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro the Dragon (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Spyro the Dragon</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Spyro the Dragon (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Spyro the Dragon (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Spyro the Dragon (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Spyro the Dragon (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Spyro the Dragon is a 1998 PlayStation third-person platformer video game developed by Insomniac Games and released by Sony Computer Entertainment America, under license by Universal Interactive Studios, in the USA on September 9, 1998.

Spyro the Dragon stars the title character, a young purple dragon named Spyro and his dragonfly friend, Sparx, and is the first game in the Spyro the Dragon series. The first game was massively popular at its initial release and Spyro would later become one of the most recognizable, popular and respected gaming icons for the PlayStation gaming console. Spyro's best friend, Sparx the dragonfly, acts like the player's health meter and assists in gathering gems. The various dragons Spyro unfreezes along the way are also key characters in Spyro's progression through the game. Gnasty Gnorc is the main antagonist, who froze all the dragons of the land in crystal.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980909T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Universal Interactive Inc., Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA).m3u</path>
		<name>Spyro - Year of the Dragon</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Spyro - Year of the Dragon (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Spyro: Year of the Dragon is a 2000 platform game developed by Insomniac Games and published by Sony Computer Entertainment for the PlayStation. Year of the Dragon is the third game in the Spyro series.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001110T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Insomniac Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment Europe</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
