<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land 2 (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land 2 (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land 2 (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Land 2 (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Donkey Kong Land 2 (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>Wage battle against Kaptain K. Rool and his vast army of Kremlings. K. Rool kidnapped Donkey Kong and he's demanding the entire Banana Hoard as ransom. It's up to Diddy Kong and Dixie Kong to rescue their kidnapped pal. A wild assortment of friendly animals like Rambi the Rhino, Squitter the Spider, Squawks the Parrot, Rattly the Rattlesnake, and Enguarde the Swordfish help the two little monkeys in their adventurous mission. Each exciting level is filled with special traps, hidden items and dastardly Kremlings! Prepare yourself for the biggest Game Boy adventure yet!</desc>
		<releasedate>19960923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land III (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land III</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land III (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land III (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Land III (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Donkey Kong Land III (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>Fame-and-fortune seekers have flooded Donkey Kong Country in search of the fabled Lost World. You command Dixie Kong and Kiddy Kong through 36 Kong-sized levels of action and adventure. Use your animal friends - Squitter the spider, Squawks the parrot, Ellie the elephant, Enguarde the swordfish and Parry the parallel bird - to help you prove your adventuring skills and find the Lost World before someone else does!

In this updated version of Donkey Kong Land III, enjoy the classic adventure now in full color exclusively released in Japan.</desc>
		<releasedate>19971030T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong Land (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong Land</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong Land (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong Land (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Donkey Kong Land (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>Monkey mayhem comes to Game Boy with all-new Kong adventures! Donkey Kong teams up with his sidekick, Diddy Kong, for new adventures and gorilla antics. Facing high-flying pigs, deadly Zingers, and reptilian Kremlings our duo swings back into action! Challenged by incredible perils they clamor their way through the mysterious pirate ship, perils in the snow, an unbelievable aquatic temple, and crazy capers in the sky. Grab a vine and join the thrills in the Land of Kong!</desc>
		<releasedate>19950626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metroid II - Return of Samus (World).gb</path>
		<name>Metroid II - Return of Samus</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Metroid II - Return of Samus (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Metroid II - Return of Samus (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Metroid II - Return of Samus (World)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Metroid II - Return of Samus (World)</cartridge>
		<desc>Metroid II: Return of Samus is a 1991 Game Boy side-scrolling metroidvania platformer video game developed by Nintendo R&amp;D1 and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on November 5, 1991.

Space Hunter Samus Aran returns to battle a planet crawling with evil creatures bent on universal domination in this bigger than ever sequel to the NES classic, Metroid.

Take control! Guide Samus through cavernous corridors, ancient ruins and alien traps. On the mysterious planet of the Metroid, you'll find artifacts of a lost civilization that grant amazing powers. Cut through creatures in a buzz-saw blur! Roll through hidden tunnels and climb sheer walls!

A battery back-up allows you to save your progress as you fight to the heart of the planet and search for the merciless Metroid leaders. If you are a cunning explorer, you'll earn the best of several super endings.

Enter this exciting Metroid sequel and experience the thrills of Game boy like never before!</desc>
		<releasedate>19911105T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Blue Version (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Blue Version</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Blue Version (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Blue Version (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon - Blue Version (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pokemon - Blue Version (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>You've finally been granted your Pokémon trainer's license. Now, it's time to head out to become the world's greatest Pokémon trainer. It's going to take all you've got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world. Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu. Face off against Blastoise's torrential water cannons. Stand strong when facing Pidgeot's stormy Gust. Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve. Important - no single Pokémon can win it all. Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the 8 GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?</desc>
		<releasedate>19980928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Red Version (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Red Version</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Red Version (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Red Version (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon - Red Version (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pokemon - Red Version (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>You've finally been granted your Pokémon trainer's license. Now, it's time to head out to become the world's greatest Pokémon trainer. It's going to take all you've got to collect 150 Pokémon in this enormous world. Catch and train monsters like the shockingly-cute Pikachu. Face off against Blastoise's torrential water cannons. Stand strong when facing Pidgeot's stormy Gust. Trade with friends and watch your Pokémon evolve. Important - no single Pokémon can win it all. Can you develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the 8 GYM Leaders and become the greatest Pokémon Master of all time?</desc>
		<releasedate>19980928T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon - Yellow Version (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Pokemon - Yellow Version</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Yellow Version (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon - Yellow Version (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon - Yellow Version (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pokemon - Yellow Version (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>You've finally earned your Pokémon trainer license, and now you're well on your way to becoming the world's greatest Pokémon trainer! The surprisingly cute Pikachu follows you around as you roam the huge world in search of monsters to train and evolve. Face off against Blastoise's torrential water gun. Stand your ground against Pidgeot's stormy flurry. Develop the ultimate Pokémon strategy to defeat the eight GYM leaders and become the greatest Pokémon master of all time!

• Compete against a friend in the new Colosseum 2 for the Pika Cup, Petite Cup and Poké Cup titles.
• Print your Pokédex data with a Game Boy printer and Game Link cable.
• Trade Pokémon with your friends using a Game Link cable. You'll need to trade with the Red and Blue versions to catch all 150 Pokémon and complete your Pokédex!</desc>
		<releasedate>20000616T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Freak</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Shock Lobster.gb</path>
		<name>Shock Lobster</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Shock Lobster</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Shock Lobster</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Shock Lobster</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cartridge>
		<desc>Venture forth on your quest as a lowly lobster imbued with magical powers, determined to inflict lethal damage to whatever stands in your way!

You start out with a handful of skills allowing you to avoid oncoming obstacles and deal damage, but will use the pearls you collect on your way to unlock more skills, upgrades, and items to push your high score higher and higher.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dave VanEe</developer>
		<publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Super Mario Land 2 - 6 Golden Coins (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>In his greatest Game Boy adventure, Mario faces off against his evil rival Wario, who has captured Mario Land and turned it into his private playground.

To toss Wario off his ill-gotten throne, Mario must search all-new worlds for the six golden coins that unlock the gate to Mario's castle. A mob of monsters, old and new, seek to stop him. Along the way, through 6 zones, Mario can nab Power Mushrooms, Super Stars and Fire Flowers for extra power. And if he eats the Magic Carrot, he'll turn into a high-flying hare.

The battery pack saves your game in progress in this biggest Game Boy Mario adventure yet.

Trailer: YouTube

ESRB Rating: E - Everyone

Genre(s): Platform</desc>
		<releasedate>20171225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land 2 - DX.gb</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land 2 - DX</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land 2 - DX</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land 2 - DX</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario Land 2 - DX</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cartridge>
		<desc>Super Mario Land 2 DX is a color hack for Super Mario Land 2 in the same vein as Link’s Awakening DX. It adds color, lets you play with Luigi (with different physics) and removes the lag.</desc>
		<releasedate>20171225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>toruzz</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land DX.gb</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land DX</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land DX</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land DX</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario Land DX</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cartridge>
		<desc>Super Mario Land DX is a romhack of the original Super Mario Land for the Game Boy that turns the game into a Game Boy Color game. It adds color and changes the graphics to give the game a modern look.</desc>
		<releasedate>20220420T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>toruzz</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario Land (World).gb</path>
		<name>Super Mario Land</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario Land (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario Land (World)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Super Mario Land (World)</cartridge>
		<desc>Journey with Mario to a land of giant crabs, Koopa Troopas, flying stone heads and hungry sharks! Travel over land, in the air, and underwater. Mario makes his way through four treacherous worlds on his way to save the Princess!</desc>
		<releasedate>19890731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tetris (World).gb</path>
		<name>Tetris</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Tetris (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tetris (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tetris (World)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tetris (World)</cartridge>
		<desc>The Soviet game sensation is now on your Game Boy! Beams, boxes, zig-zags and L-shaped blocks drop down a narrow passage. Feel your pulse quicken as you spin, shift and align the shapes for a perfect fit. It's challenging and demands split-second decision making! Start at new heights for a tougher contest. Pick the music and set your pace from 20 progressive skill levels!</desc>
		<releasedate>19890731T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman! (USA, Europe).gb</path>
		<name>Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman!</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman! (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman! (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman! (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Wario Blast Featuring Bomberman! (USA, Europe)</cartridge>
		<desc>Wario Blast: Featuring Bomberman! is a 1994 Game Boy maze action video game developed by Hudson Soft and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on November 15, 1994.

OH NO! Wario has stumbled upon the secret gateway into Bomberland! Now the greedy warmonger wants to claim the land, its inhabitants, and treasures as his own. Entering the underground labyrinth, he meets the resistance of the Madbombers - explosives experts who have some TNT tricks and surprises to toss at Wario. The battle heats up as Wario and Bomberman each try to outwit the other, level by level in a dynamite duel!</desc>
		<releasedate>19941115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Soft</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wario Land (World).gb</path>
		<name>Wario Land</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Wario Land (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Wario Land (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Wario Land (World)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Wario Land (World)</cartridge>
		<desc>Desiring to replace or restore the castle he lost to his rival in Super Mario Land 2: 6 Golden Coins, Wario sets out to steal a golden statue of Princess Toadstool from the Brown Sugar Pirates and Captain Syrup, which he then intends to ransom for the money to buy his own castle. Along the way, he collects or steals any other coins and treasures he finds or knocks out of enemies. The game is spent by navigating a number of levels to reclaim his lost treasures, and has a significant level of re-playability due to the branched path that many of the levels take. In the end, Captain Syrup (revealed to be female, which was hidden in the instruction manual) is defeated while Wario ultimately gets anything from a birdhouse to an actual planet or moon for himself based on the amount of treasure collected as compensation for failing to steal the statue (due to Mario retrieving it by airlifting it)</desc>
		<releasedate>19940201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo R&amp;D1</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
