<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Action and Puzzles and Bears, Oh My!

Trouble brews when Gruntilda the witch captures the unbearably beautiful cub, Tooty. But before the grisly hag can steal the bear's good looks, big brother Banjo and his fine-feathered friend, Kazooie, join forces to stop her. Combining their 24 moves and special powers, Banjo and Kazooie will fend off armies of beasts. Bear and bird must hunt down the 100 puzzle pieces and 900 musical notes that will ultimately lead them to Gruntilda. However, miles of swamp, desert and snow and one bear of an adventure stand in their way.

-Soar over islands to scout out buried treasure.

-Brave past whirling blades in the belly of a mechanical shark.

-With some voodoo magic, transform into different creatures to gain special powers.

-Solve the puzzles of the ancients to unearth the cursed labyrinths.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Tooie (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Tooie</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Grunty returns-and that's bad news for Banjo and Kazooie! In this all-new adventure, combine everything you learned in the award-winning prequel, Banjo-Kazooie, with dozens of brand-new moves and abilities. Explore eight original worlds-like a monstrous factory and a dilapidated amusement park. Solve incredible puzzles that link those worlds together-sometimes you'll have to complete tasks in several worlds to solve a single puzzle!

-Divide and conquer! The bear and bird are back and this time they can split up and work alone.

-Play as Mumbo! Now you'll get to take control of the bone-headed shaman himself!

-Meet Humba Wumba! She'll transform Banjo into a number of objects, such as a walkin', talkin' statue or a tightie whitie shootin' washer.

-Four-player mini-games! Play over a dozen mini-games, including five different shootout modes.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Before Reinhardt Schneider and Carrie Fernandez confronted Dracula, a magical warrior embarked on a quest that would ultimately lead him to Dracula's lair. Take control of Cornell, a powerful werewolf, who is seeking out the evil minions responsible for his sister's disappearance. Armed with the power to morph from human to werewolf, Cornell is destined to rescure his sister from a sinister plan and rid the world of Dracula once and for all. Will he succeed or fail? Will the past unravel the future? Discover the legacy in this exciting prequel.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bottom Up</developer>
		<publisher>Bottom Up</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Conker's Bad Fur Day</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Conker's Bad Fur Day is a 2001 N64 third-person action-adventure platformer video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on March 5, 2001.

The guys at Rare have been very, very naughty.

The day after his 21st birthday bash, Conker's sporting the worst hangover ever, and he just can't seem to find his way home. Prepare to stagger through randy, raunchy, raucous scenarios crammed full of bad manners, twisted humor, and graphic bodily functions. Unless you're a fan of violence, foul language, and racy innuendo, you'd best steer clear of this one.

* Warped characters... Meet slow-witted farm implements, a well-endowed sunflower, and a mysterious beast known only as the Great Mighty Poo.
* Bizarre Behaviors... Transform into a vampire's guano-dropping lackey, battle a caveman whose bone is worse than his bite, and storm the beach in an amphibious assault on an army of sinister stuffed bears.
* Frenetic multiplayer modes... Team up with friends or go it alone in seven different multiplayer games or five different free-for-all arenas.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Diddy Kong Racing is a 1997 N64 racing video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on November 24, 1997.

Timber the Tiger's parents picked a fine time to go on vacation. When they come back, they're going to be faced with an island trashed by the spiteful space bully Wizpig - unless the local animals can do something about it! So join Diddy Kong as he teams up with Timber the Tiger, Pipsy the Mouse and Taj the Genie in an epic racing adventure unlike anything you've ever experienced before!

-This unique game blends adventure and racing like no other game!

-Roam anywhere you want on the island by car, plane or hovercraft!

-An enormous amount of single player and multiplayer modes!

-Feel the action when you use the N64™ Rumble Pak™ and save your times on the N64™ Controller Pak™!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM) - Secondary Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>K. Rool has ape-napped the Kongs!

Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Pony Tail Twirl. Even Rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!

-Don't forget the mini-games! Challenge a seal to a race around the lagoon, go on a crazy mine cart ride, and be on the lookout for a blast from the past...

-Four players can join in on super split-screen action or duke it out in a single-screen free-for-all!

-Use of the required Expansion Pak (included) allows incredible real-time lighting effects and massive environments.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X (USA).z64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/F-Zero X (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/F-Zero X (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/F-Zero X (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/F-Zero X (USA)</cart>
		<desc>F-Zero X is a 1998 N64 racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on October 26, 1998.

It's you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You're racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won't shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!

• Saves via Internal Memory (SRAM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>GoldenEye 007 is a 1997 N64 first-person shooter video game developed by Rare and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on August 25, 1997.

You are Bond, James Bond.

You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!

Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!

* Exciting 3D environments.
* Highly intelligent enemies!
* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!
* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask [redux].z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Majora's Mask [redux]</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask [redux]</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask [redux]</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask [redux]</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Majora’s Mask Redux is a hack that aims to improve the original experience of Majora’s Mask by adding some QoL improvements by applying the ASM patches provided by the Majora’s Mask Randomizer project by Saneki and its contributors.</desc>
		<releasedate>20201124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maroc</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Majora's Mask</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Link's all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above. When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Master of Time.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Master of Time</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Master of Time</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Master of Time</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Master of Time</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>After saving both Hyrule and Termina, Link found himself without a quest. He journeyed long and far without knowing what to do. He thought a lot about the time manipulation he had done and asked himself if he was the real hero or if he was just a victim of these stories.

The more his obsession of time had grown, the more it felt that time was slowing down… Until it froze completely, condemning his journey to an endless day… Just before passing out from exhaustion, Link finally found a new country…

Master of Time is a new story in a completely new world, Abello, where Link must restore the flow of time. Abello is a big and dangerous world, but Link can count on the help of Nite the fairy.

Around 20 hours of gameplay in various areas and dungeons with custom cutscenes, songs and much more. Good luck finding all 100 skulltula tokens and 20 hearts!</desc>
		<releasedate>20200713T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Don Camilo</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time [redux].z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time [redux]</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time [redux]</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time [redux]</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time [redux]</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>This hack aims at improving the original experience of Ocarina of Time by adding some QoL improvements by applying the ASM patches provided by the Ocarina of Time Randomizer project by Roman971 and its contributors. (NOTE: For a full list of the Credits per-dev, please check the ReadMe. Adult Link 3D model made by SkilarBabcock, with permission to use for this project: https://youtu.be/x6MIeEZIsPw)</desc>
		<releasedate>20201124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Maroc</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Sealed Palace.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Sealed Palace</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Sealed Palace</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Sealed Palace</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Sealed Palace</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>An Ocarina of Time Romhack. Lots of gameplay in various areas and dungeons with custom cutscenes, songs and much more. Good luck finding all 100 Skulltula tokens and 20 hearts!</desc>
		<releasedate>20230419T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Jinnosuke9</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - The Missing Link.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - The Missing Link</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - The Missing Link</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - The Missing Link</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - The Missing Link</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>This mini-adventure is set in between Ocarina of Time and Majora’s Mask. It follows Link on his quest to find Navi, his fairy companion from the first N64 Zelda game.

But this search for a missing friend quickly turns into an urgent rescue mission. And if Link doesn’t find Navi soon, the entire world will be at risk.

The creators crafted new environments, graphics and music. During your quest you’ll find a new item and gameplay mechanics that go along with it.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ultimate Trial.z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ultimate Trial</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ultimate Trial</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ultimate Trial</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Ultimate Trial</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Link and Navi find themselves deep within the Lost Woods as they stumble upon a mysterious stronghold. Not knowing what will await them, they are courageous enough to enter it.

Ultimate Trial includes new characters, locations, and music as well as custom enemies and upgradeable equipment within a new, unique story. A guide will be released in a couple of days as well as the soundtrack.

Enjoy the game at your own pace by setting the difficulty in the pause menu screen.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240716T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ultimate Trial Team</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Golf</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Golf (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Golf (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Golf (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Mario Golf (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Forget buying expensive golf gear--Mario brings the game to you. Mario Golf features four complete 18-hole courses, 11 golfers, and precise play control. Create your own golfer and build up his or her experience and skill levels by competing in various tournaments and head-to-head matches. The more you play, the stronger and more accurate your golfer becomes. There are many different modes of play in Mario Golf, including a wide variety of minigames designed to challenge even the most level-headed swingers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 - Amped Up.z64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64 - Amped Up</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 - Amped Up</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 - Amped Up</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Kart 64 - Amped Up</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>This is a mod for the game Mario Kart 64.
It adds 16 brand new courses, as well as additional game modes, music, modern visuals, gameplay techniques, and much more!</desc>
		<releasedate>20210101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Litronom</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Racing, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 is a 1997 N64 racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on February 10, 1997.

Three… Two… One… GO! The signal light changes and you drop the pedal to the metal. Take on up to three friends in the split-screen VS games, or race solo in the Mario GP. Tell your friends to bring it on in the highly competitive Battle mode. Advanced features allow you to race with your “Ghost”. The driving data from your best run appears as a transparent character on the screen. No longer must you simply race against the clock -- you can actually race against yourself!

-Save your hottest Ghost data to a portable N64 Controller Pak™ (Sold Separately)

-Collect multiple power-up items!

-Twenty different courses -- 4 Cups with 4 courses each and 4 special Battle mode courses!

-Everyone’s favorite characters are back and gorgeously rendered, including two new additions, Donkey Kong™ and Wario™!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Party 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Mario and the gang are back for another round of Bowser-bashin' party action! Watch as your favorite Nintendo characters don different duds for each of the five all-new Adventure Boards! A slew of new tricks and devices bring new levels of challenge and excitement to board game play. New board maps, new Mini-Games, new action and new surprises means a whole new batch of fun! Get ready to unleash your best Hip Drops, hammer swings and high-flying high junks for another round of frenzied multi-player action!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Tennis (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Tennis (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Tennis (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Mario Tennis (USA)</cart>
		<desc>All of your favorite characters hit the court in a wild and wacky multiplayer tennis game from the makers of Mario Golf. Mario, Luigi, Bowser, Peach, Toad, and Donkey Kong lead off the all-star, 14-player line-up. The fast-paced action will have you unleashing vicious volleys, life-saving lobs, ballistic backhands and electrifying super-charged smashes!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>20000828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Paper Mario (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Paper Mario (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Paper Mario (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Paper Mario (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Paper Mario is a role-playing game developed by Intelligent Systems for the Nintendo 64. It was later re-released for the iQue Player in 2004, the Wii's Virtual Console in 2007, the Wii U's Virtual Console in 2015, and Nintendo 64 - Nintendo Switch Online in 2021.

Paper Mario has the player taking control of Mario on his quest to rescue Princess Peach and save the Mushroom Kingdom from Bowser, who has stolen the mythical Star Rod of Star Haven and used its wish-granting powers to make himself invincible. To stop Bowser and rescue Princess Peach, Mario and company must save the seven Star Spirits; magical beings who have been sealed in cards by Bowser with the power to nullify the Star Rod, as well as the original owners of the Star Rod.

Paper Mario's gameplay is a blend of traditional Japanese role-playing games and Mario-esque platforming features; Mario has the ability to jump in both the overworld and in battle, and jumping remains one of the most important actions in the game. The player controls Mario and a party of followers as they journey through the Mushroom Kingdom, exploring dungeons, managing stats, and battling enemies. The title refers to the game's arts and crafts aesthetic; nearly every character in the game is drawn as a flat 2D sprite, revealing itself as paper-thin when turning around, and many elements of the environments are also depicted as 2D sprites.

Paper Mario was initially in development for the Nintendo 64DD under the name Super Mario RPG 2[5] (also called Mario RPG 2[6] or Mario RPG 64[7]) and intended as a sequel to Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars. Concept art posted by Super Mario RPG artist Kazuyuki Kurashima on his Instagram account in 2019 indicated that Samus Aran and Link from the Metroid and The Legend of Zelda franchises would have appeared alongside Mario characters.[8] It later became the first installment of the Paper Mario series and would go on to receive several sequels; the first in the same style of gameplay (Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door), followed by four in different playstyles (Super Paper Mario, Paper Mario: Sticker Star, Paper Mario: Color Splash, and Paper Mario: The Origami King).

The above text is from the Super Mario Wiki and is available under a Creative Commons license. Attribution must be provided through a list of authors or a link back to the original article. Source: https://www.mariowiki.com/Paper_Mario</desc>
		<releasedate>20000811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Perfect Dark (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Perfect Dark (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Perfect Dark (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Perfect Dark (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Perfect Dark is a 2000 N64 first-person shooter video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on May 22, 2000.

Step into the dark... As Carrington Institute's most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation's recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM) - Secondary Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Snap (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokemon Snap</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon Snap (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</cart>
		<desc>The Professor has asked you to capture the Wild Pokémon of Pokémon Island… on film!  Tour the island in your ZERO-ONE vehicle and snap pictures of Pokémon in their natural habitat.  Wild Pokémon are often camera-shy, so you’ll have to use special items to bring them out in the open.  Only the best shots will do for the Professor’s Pokémon Report, so sharpen your photography skills and get ready to SNAP!
* The first-ever N64 game to feature the world-famous Pokémon--fully rendered in 3-D!
* Explore the many environments of Pokémon Island, like the sunny beach, the mysterious caves, and even a red-hot volcano!
* Many different types of Pokémon inhabit the island.  See how many you can catch on film!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter, Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokemon Stadium 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>At long last, all of your favorite Pokémon are rady to go head-to-head on the N64®! Whether you're battle a friend, a Gym Leader or a tournament contestant, you're about to witness some of the most spectacular battle scenes in Pokémon history! Select a team from a huge stable of "rental" battlers, or use the included N64 Transfer Pak™ to upload your own team from Pokémon Red, Blue or Yellow! This Stadium is packed and ready to rock!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Fox 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Star Fox 64 (Japanese: スターフォックス64 Hepburn: Sutā Fokkusu Rokujūyon?), known in Australia and Europe as Lylat Wars, is a 3D scrolling shooter game themed around aircraft combat for the Nintendo 64 video game console. It is a reboot of the original Star Fox, and the only game in the Star Fox series to be released on the Nintendo 64. An autostereoscopic remake, titled Star Fox 64 3D, was released for the Nintendo 3DS in 2011.

Star Fox 64 was the first Nintendo 64 game to have included support for the Rumble Pak, with which it initially came bundled. The game received critical acclaim for its smooth animation, detailed visuals, voice acting, and use of multiple gameplay paths.

Star Fox 64 is set on a group of planets in the Lylat system. Ingenious scientist Andross, a native of the fourth planet Corneria, is driven to madness and nearly destroys the planet using biological weapons. For Andross' treason, General Pepper exiles the scientist to the remote planet Venom. Five years after Andross' exile, Pepper detects suspicious activity on Venom.[7] Pepper hires the Star Fox team (consisting of James McCloud, Peppy Hare, and Pigma Dengar) to investigate. When the three arrive at Venom, Pigma betrays the team, which causes James and Peppy to be captured by Andross. Peppy escapes and tells James' son, Fox McCloud, about his father's fate.

A few years later, Andross launches an attack across the Lylat system. Realizing that his army cannot stop Andross, Pepper summons the Star Fox team, now consisting of Fox, Peppy, Falco Lombardi and Slippy Toad.[8] While traveling through several planets, including the Lylat system's star, Solar, and the asteroid field Meteo, the team battles with several of Andross' henchmen, including the rival mercenaries, Star Wolf.

Story:
After arriving in Venom, Fox defeats Andross, but discovers that it is actually a robotic version of himself and destroys it, leaving Andross drifting in the Lylat System. Fox decides to redeem himself by returning to Venom and defeat Star Wolf once again. When Fox defeats Andross once more, he reveals his true form, a floating brain with two floating eyes. After killing Andross, James appears to show Fox the way out, then vanishes immediately after. Escaping the lair's destruction, Star Fox returns to Corneria for a victory celebration, as the game's end credits roll.

When offered membership into the Cornerian Army, Fox declines on behalf of his team; saying "Oh no, sir. We prefer doing things our own way". The game ends with the Great Fox and the Star Fox team flying off in their Arwings into the skies.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I - Racer</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Join Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars race of your life! Relive all the thrills and excitement of the Podracer sequence from Star Wars: Episode I. Hang on tight - with afterburners on, Podracers max out at a simulated 600 mph! Race in furious competition against more than 21 opponents! Take on over 21 tracks in 8 unique worlds. Avoid hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers and Tusken Raiders! Featuring spectacular 3D environments!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19990518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - B3313.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - B3313</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - B3313</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - B3313</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - B3313</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Will you play the game, or will the game play you?

B3313 or Build 3313 (also called SM64 Internal Plexus) is a ROM hack of Super Mario 64 developed by ChrisRLillo and his dev team. It is the largest beta-based SM64 hack to date in terms of the number of accessible areas and star count, as well as various other aspects.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>ChrisRLillo et al.</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Beyond the Cursed Mirror.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Beyond the Cursed Mirror</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Beyond the Cursed Mirror</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Beyond the Cursed Mirror</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Beyond the Cursed Mirror</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Greetings Superstar,
Did you know that your nemesis hid in the decrepit castle all this time? It appears he fosters his strength in a hidden compartment behind one cursed mirror. I implore you to defeat him, once and for all – for the sake of the kingdom.
-Yours truly, The Showrunner</desc>
		<releasedate>20230518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>rovertronic</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Decades Later.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Decades Later</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Decades Later</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Decades Later</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Decades Later</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Ever wondered what SM64's levels would look like after a few years, maybe even 2 decades after the events the original when Bowser took over the Castle with now 150 new stars to collect? Well, this hack aims to recreate and reimagine vanilla SM64 levels from memory to an extend where some levels will feel familiar yet new and others that have been turned into fully new levels. Stars or sections that felt too repetitive or just weren't fun in the eyes of the hack creator have been replaced with newer stars or been reworked to play out differently.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BroDute</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Escape from the Jail.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Escape from the Jail</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Escape from the Jail</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Escape from the Jail</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Escape from the Jail</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Escape from the Jail "Definitive Edition" is a hack that contains 50 stars for an adventurer to collect - remaster of an original hack made by TheGael95. Mario was captured in the jail and now he needs to find out who is behind it! Join Mario in this epic journey featuring 5 full courses and lots of side courses to explore.</desc>
		<releasedate>20220204T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>aglab2</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Eureka.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Eureka</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Eureka</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Eureka</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Eureka</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Full 100 star hack with plenty of things to find. Some useful, some not. That is for you to decide.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240414T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>GooseDaJuice</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Last Impact.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Last Impact</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Last Impact</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Last Impact</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Last Impact</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>SM64: Last Impact is a major hack made by Kaze Emanuar. It was released on September 30th, 2016. It contains 130 stars, 12 power-ups, many new bosses and a large variety of completely new levels.

In this hack, Mario only has 6 health instead of the normal 8 and a separate gauge for air underwater. This hack presents many things that weren't in previous hacks or the original game, including new power-ups, custom music and objects, and unique boss fights.</desc>
		<releasedate>20160930T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Monstrous Manor.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Monstrous Manor</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Monstrous Manor</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Monstrous Manor</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Monstrous Manor</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Mario gets invited to explore a haunted manor in this unconventionally-structured major hack.

Solve puzzles, collect keys, and fight enemies to uncover the mystery of the manor.</desc>
		<releasedate>20230929T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>MrComit</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Mystery of the Capsmith DEMO.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Mystery of the Capsmith DEMO</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Mystery of the Capsmith DEMO</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Mystery of the Capsmith DEMO</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Mystery of the Capsmith DEMO</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>The demo for Mystery of the Capsmith is here!
3 new caps, 3 new levels!

I made this game in 17 days for the Scuttle Hacking Competition and it won first place. This shorter competition/demo version doesn't have the story of the Capsmith, but the full version will. You guys can let me know what you think of it, and if you'd like to see it made into a larger hack or even a major hack.
This demo does not support N64 as its build doesn't have my newer optimizations.</desc>
		<releasedate>20221011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dorrieal</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Peach's Fury.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Peach's Fury</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Peach's Fury</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Peach's Fury</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Peach's Fury</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>This hack features a complete refactoring of the SM64 code to allow it to run high poly maps on a real N64. There is an option to turn on 60FPS mode in the pause menu. It's on by default on emu, off on N64.</desc>
		<releasedate>20220205T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze, thelegendofzeina</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 [QoL].z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 [QoL]</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 [QoL]</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 [QoL]</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 [QoL]</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Super Mario 64 'Quality of Life' update. Widescreen, cleaner camera, cleaner hud etc.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240626T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>AuryArthan</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Return to Yoshi's Island DEMO.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Return to Yoshi's Island DEMO</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Return to Yoshi's Island DEMO</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Return to Yoshi's Island DEMO</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Return to Yoshi's Island DEMO</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Bowser has kidnapped most of the Yoshi's and is forcing them to work for him. A lone orange Yoshi that napped through the kidnapping calls upon Mario to help rescue the Yoshi's.

Fall damage has not been disabled, but the distance Mario can fall without taking damage has been increased, and Mario's lives counter has been disabled.

Upon initial entry, each course will have a cutscene play that shows off the level's notable features, similar to in Last Impact. The camera controls and Stars are very similar to those used in Peach's Fury.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210415T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Royal Legacy.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Royal Legacy</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Royal Legacy</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Royal Legacy</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Royal Legacy</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>For fans of SM64 Sapphire: a new 30-star adventure awaits you. This is a very traditional platformer hack meant to challenge players who have already mastered everything vanilla SM64 asks of you. 4 original worlds, complete with a hub, Bowser stage and fight. The entire soundtrack is original music composed just for this game.</desc>
		<releasedate>20240811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>StunningCactus</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Serene Fusion.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Serene Fusion</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Serene Fusion</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Serene Fusion</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Serene Fusion</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Serene Fusion is a major ROM hack created by aglab2 and made in collaboration with the SM64 ROM hack Community for the Fangame Marathon 2022 Special Event. This hack is initially dubbed Project 74 as a remaster of Lugmillord's Super Mario 74, which contains a couple levels from the original hack with newer gimmicks and redesigns. It features a total of 80 Stars and over 8 levels; additionally, original level content is included as main and secret stages alike.</desc>
		<releasedate>20221009T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Aglab2</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Shotgun Mario.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Shotgun Mario</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Shotgun Mario</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Shotgun Mario</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Shotgun Mario</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Shotgun Mario 64 is a ROM hack created by Dorrieal. The majority of this hack uses the same content as vanilla Super Mario 64 (such as levels and areas), but its stand-out custom mechanic, a shotgun, sets it apart from other vanilla edits. Not because it's a gun, but because of the execution of this custom mechanic.

Note for speedrunners: hold R, Z and B during the intro to skip the tutorial.

Upon starting a new file, Mario will enter a quick tutorial on the basics of using his shotgun. He will not, however, be taught the extent of how this mechanic can affect the world around him. Using the shotgun not only annihilates enemies, but many of the objects and facets of the overworld/levels have had custom behaviour added in, so that shotgunning them often causes some bizarre effect. Here are a few examples of the many custom behaviours:
- Doors can now be blown off their hinges.
- Trees can sustain multiple forms of damage and will also be left singed.
- Cannon hatches can be destroyed, thus giving the Bob-omb Buddies a permanent holiday.
- Power Stars undergo a divorce upon being shot.
- Lakitu skip has never been easier.
There are many, many others, but this hack is best experienced without knowing much of what will happen.</desc>
		<releasedate>20231022T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Dorrieal</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Star Revenge 6.25 - Luigi's Adventure DX.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Star Revenge 6.25 - Luigi's Adventure DX</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Star Revenge 6.25 - Luigi's Adventure DX</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Star Revenge 6.25 - Luigi's Adventure DX</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Star Revenge 6.25 - Luigi's Adventure DX</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>After his brother has vanished, Luigi finds himself in mysterious castle inside a forest that has been overran by bad guys like Bowser.</desc>
		<releasedate>20191218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BroDute</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Star Road.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Star Road</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Star Road</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Star Road</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Star Road</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Super Mario Star Road is a ROM Hack made by Skelux. It was released around Christmas 2011, and contains 130 Stars. This ROM hack is considered to be one of the most famous. It contains levels with similar design to the original Super Mario 64, which is overall very solid and fun.

This hack tries to be a sequel, or another version, of the original Super Mario 64, in terms of level design, difficulty, and plot. Not only are all of the levels redone using custom graphics (some of which directly come from other Nintendo 64 games), but custom music and custom enemies have been added as well. The level entrances range from simple pipes or paintings to more unconventional entrances, such as a vase or an easel. In addition, the boss fights have been changed; Bowser himself is only fought once in the game, at the end of the final Bowser level. In the first two Bowser levels, Mario must defeat a mini-boss in order to obtain the key to the next area.

(Information from the Mario 64 Hacks Wiki)</desc>
		<releasedate>20111224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Skelux</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Through the Ages.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Through the Ages</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Through the Ages</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Through the Ages</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Through the Ages</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Mario visits various historical locations while teaming up with various partner Pokemon.

NOTE: DO NOT PLAY ON PARALLEL PLUGIN! GlideN64 is strongly recommended for the best experience.</desc>
		<releasedate>20220430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Kaze</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Super Mario 64 is a 1996 N64 third-person platformer video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on September 26, 1996.

Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive soundtrack, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis -- Bowser, King of the Koopas!

-Run freely in a grassy meadow, tip-toe through a gloomy dungeon, climb to the top of a mountain or take a swim in the moat!

-Leap head first into a watery painting and soon you'll be searching for the surface in an underwater realm!

-On-the-fly, 3D rendered game play delivers the action of ruthless enemy attacks from every angle!

-Find the Caps that give Mario super powers, ponder the mysteries of the pyramid, you can even race Koopas for fabulous prizes!

-With the Nintendo 64 Controller and its analog Control Stick, Mario can crawl, kick down obstacles, swim, do reverse flips, and even stick the landing on his backwards somersault!

-Saved game information is stored for up to four players in memory.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 - Vacation Course.z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64 - Vacation Course</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Vacation Course</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 - Vacation Course</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 - Vacation Course</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/00Placeholder</cart>
		<desc>Play this open-world 30-star hack inspired by Bowser's Fury! Placed 1st in scuttlebug_raiser's 1st Hacking Competition, hosted on the SM64Romhacks discord server.</desc>
		<releasedate>20210416T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Reonu</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking</publisher>
		<genre>Platform, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Super Smash Bros. is a 1999 N64 crossover fighting video game developed by HAL Laboratory and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on April 26, 1999.

It's a Bumpin', Bruisin', Brawlin' Bash!

The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!

-Plunge headlong into battle with your favorite Nintendo characters: Mario, Link, Donkey Kong, Pikachu, Samus, Yoshi, Kirby and Fox... plus 4 hidden characters!

-Characters use their own trademark attacks, such as Mario’s fireballs and Link’s sword.

-Grab a Fire Flower or Poké Ball and send your opponent sailing out of the arena.

-Compete in 8 different settings, each from a character’s home world and each with its own dangers.

• Saves via Internal Memory (SRAM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion picks up where Turok 2: Seeds of Evil left off when gamers were first introduced to "Oblivion" and its lackeys, 'Flesh Eaters. Oblivion is a monstrous cosmic entity that consumed everything in its path. It reigned before the birth of our universe. Invading the bodies of the living and devouring them from the inside-out, Oblivion fed on the very energy of the dead and dying. When the Primagen's Lightship was destroyed, the chain reaction it triggered as a result was so powerful that the universe as it existed was completely eradicated, and the almighty Oblivion was pushed to the very brink of destruction. For the first time, Oblivion felt pain, fear, and hate. Though totally ravaged, Oblivion survived and now desperately seeks a means to punch through the Netherscape that separates our world from the Lost Lands (a strange and primitive world where "time has no meaning"), and the Lost Lands from countless others. The last shreds of the pure energy source that created our world and nearly wiped out Oblivion are contained within the Light Burden, the bag that every member of the Turok lineage has carried. The death of the Turok mantle will signal the beginning of the end: the rebirth of Oblivion.

• Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>20000830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Story (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Story</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Yoshi's Story (USA)</marquee>
		<cart>./00Cart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</cart>
		<desc>Yoshi's Story is a 1998 N64 side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on March 10, 1998.

Baby Bowser has taken the Super Happy Tree and cast a spell on Yoshi's world, turning it into the pages of a picture book. The only Yoshies not affected by the spell were six hatchlings that were still protected by their shells. It's up to them to reclaim the Super Happy Tree and restore happiness to the world. That is the only thing that can break Baby Bowser's Spell!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19980310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
