<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA).z64</path>
		<name>1080 Snowboarding</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/1080 Snowboarding (Japan, USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>You’re taking a Tahoe 155 snowboard down a steep, bumpy incline at night and you’re about to top off an Indy Nosebone with a 360 Air, and you haven’t even left your living room! You’re Playing 1080 (Ten Eighty) Snowboarding, a game so intense you’ll be brushing the snow off your goggles. With five different boarders, eight different Lamar snowboards, more than 25 tricks, a Half-Pipe and six different courses, this is as close as you’ll get to the real thing without hopping on the next ski lift.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980401T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Kazooie (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Kazooie</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Banjo-Kazooie (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Action and Puzzles and Bears, Oh My!

Trouble brews when Gruntilda the witch captures the unbearably beautiful cub, Tooty. But before the grisly hag can steal the bear's good looks, big brother Banjo and his fine-feathered friend, Kazooie, join forces to stop her. Combining their 24 moves and special powers, Banjo and Kazooie will fend off armies of beasts. Bear and bird must hunt down the 100 puzzle pieces and 900 musical notes that will ultimately lead them to Gruntilda. However, miles of swamp, desert and snow and one bear of an adventure stand in their way.

-Soar over islands to scout out buried treasure.

-Brave past whirling blades in the belly of a mechanical shark.

-With some voodoo magic, transform into different creatures to gain special powers.

-Solve the puzzles of the ancients to unearth the cursed labyrinths.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981206T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Banjo-Tooie (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Banjo-Tooie</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Banjo-Tooie (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Grunty returns-and that's bad news for Banjo and Kazooie! In this all-new adventure, combine everything you learned in the award-winning prequel, Banjo-Kazooie, with dozens of brand-new moves and abilities. Explore eight original worlds-like a monstrous factory and a dilapidated amusement park. Solve incredible puzzles that link those worlds together-sometimes you'll have to complete tasks in several worlds to solve a single puzzle!

-Divide and conquer! The bear and bird are back and this time they can split up and work alone.

-Play as Mumbo! Now you'll get to take control of the bone-headed shaman himself!

-Meet Humba Wumba! She'll transform Banjo into a number of objects, such as a walkin', talkin' statue or a tightie whitie shootin' washer.

-Four-player mini-games! Play over a dozen mini-games, including five different shootout modes.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001127T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Body Harvest (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Body Harvest</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Body Harvest (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Body Harvest (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Body Harvest (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Body Harvest (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The year is 2016. Humanity has been reduced to a few survivors inhabiting the orbital space station Omega. Over the course of the history, aliens visited the Earth every twenty-five years, "harvesting" humans as an organic material. Eventually, they launch an assault on the last remnants of the human race. But Adam Drake, a genetically engineered soldier, comes into possession of a time-traveling device. He uses it to travel to the time periods of human history when aliens performed their deadly attacks. The fate of humanity is in his hands.

Body Harvest is an action and driving game with a mission-based structure. The protagonist travels to various locations and eras (e.g. Greece during World War II, Siberia in the 1990s, etc.) with the goal of stopping alien invasions. Missions can be accessed by traveling to specified areas on the map. Adam can move on foot and use his weapons to kill aliens; however, vehicles usually prove to be a more reliable way of tackling most missions. Adam can use most of his weapons while in a vehicle; in addition, some vehicles are outfitted with their own weapons.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>DMA Design Limited</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Castlevania - Legacy of Darkness (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Before Reinhardt Schneider and Carrie Fernandez confronted Dracula, a magical warrior embarked on a quest that would ultimately lead him to Dracula's lair. Take control of Cornell, a powerful werewolf, who is seeking out the evil minions responsible for his sister's disappearance. Armed with the power to morph from human to werewolf, Cornell is destined to rescure his sister from a sinister plan and rid the world of Dracula once and for all. Will he succeed or fail? Will the past unravel the future? Discover the legacy in this exciting prequel.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991225T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bottom Up</developer>
		<publisher>Bottom Up</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Conker's Bad Fur Day</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Conker's Bad Fur Day (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Conker's Bad Fur Day is a 2001 N64 third-person action-adventure platformer video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on March 5, 2001.

The guys at Rare have been very, very naughty.

The day after his 21st birthday bash, Conker's sporting the worst hangover ever, and he just can't seem to find his way home. Prepare to stagger through randy, raunchy, raucous scenarios crammed full of bad manners, twisted humor, and graphic bodily functions. Unless you're a fan of violence, foul language, and racy innuendo, you'd best steer clear of this one.

* Warped characters... Meet slow-witted farm implements, a well-endowed sunflower, and a mysterious beast known only as the Great Mighty Poo.
* Bizarre Behaviors... Transform into a vampire's guano-dropping lackey, battle a caveman whose bone is worse than his bite, and storm the beach in an amphibious assault on an army of sinister stuffed bears.
* Frenetic multiplayer modes... Team up with friends or go it alone in seven different multiplayer games or five different free-for-all arenas.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010305T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Diddy Kong Racing (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Diddy Kong Racing is a 1997 N64 racing video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on November 24, 1997.

Timber the Tiger's parents picked a fine time to go on vacation. When they come back, they're going to be faced with an island trashed by the spiteful space bully Wizpig - unless the local animals can do something about it! So join Diddy Kong as he teams up with Timber the Tiger, Pipsy the Mouse and Taj the Genie in an epic racing adventure unlike anything you've ever experienced before!

-This unique game blends adventure and racing like no other game!

-Roam anywhere you want on the island by car, plane or hovercraft!

-An enormous amount of single player and multiplayer modes!

-Feel the action when you use the N64™ Rumble Pak™ and save your times on the N64™ Controller Pak™!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM) - Secondary Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Donkey Kong 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>K. Rool has ape-napped the Kongs!

Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Pony Tail Twirl. Even Rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!

-Don't forget the mini-games! Challenge a seal to a race around the lagoon, go on a crazy mine cart ride, and be on the lookout for a blast from the past...

-Four players can join in on super split-screen action or duke it out in a single-screen free-for-all!

-Use of the required Expansion Pak (included) allows incredible real-time lighting effects and massive environments.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Excitebike 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Excitebike 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Excitebike 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Excitebike 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Excitebike 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Excitebike 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Experience extreme MX! You grind your way through the hairpin turn, a wall of mud exploding in your wake. Your next jump launches you into the air - you pull off a spectacular double no-footed can-can and become an instant legend! In Excitebike 64, you'll find all the high-flying action, heart-stopping stunts and bone-jarring crashes of the extreme sport of motocross. It'll set the daredevil inside you free. 20 stadium tracks and awesome outdoor courses - plus six different riders with six unique styles!</desc>
		<releasedate>20000430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Left Field Productions</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Forsaken 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Forsaken 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Forsaken 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Forsaken 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Forsaken 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Forsaken 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Forsaken is a first-person shoot 'em up in which you have complete movement freedom in 3 dimensions, as you accelerate, swerve and strafe your craft, making for gameplay resembling Descent. Each level has a defined exit which must be reached within a tight time limit. The surrounding areas are collapsing around you, with spikes and turbine fans among your hazards. Be very aware of other craft out to take all you have, as they alter their approach based on your weaponry (from the 25 featured in the game) and past encounters.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Iguana Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./F-Zero X (USA).z64</path>
		<name>F-Zero X</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/F-Zero X (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/F-Zero X (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/F-Zero X (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/F-Zero X (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>F-Zero X is a 1998 N64 racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on October 26, 1998.

It's you against 29 other machines competing for the title of F-Zero X Champion. You're racing at speeds of over 1,000 km/h high above the atmosphere. Your competition comes from every corner of the galaxy and won't shed a tear at the thought of smashing you off the track. With four-player simultaneous gameplay and the Rumble Pak accessory, you have the fastest racing game on the N64 system!

• Saves via Internal Memory (SRAM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19981026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Goemon's Great Adventure (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Goemon's Great Adventure</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Goemon's Great Adventure (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Goemon's Great Adventure (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Goemon's Great Adventure (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Goemon's Great Adventure (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Goemon and all his friends are back in his greatest adventure yet! Goemon's Great Adventure combines classic Goemon platform action with an all-new twist. The evil time-traveling nun, Bismaru, has summoned Dochuki, a demon prince, to take over the Earth. But first, she wants to marry him! Can Goemon and his gang stop the demon? Can Dochuki escape the cloying clutches of the wacked-out nun? Will Ebisu ever beat his own dumpling eating record? It's an adventure you'll never forget!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990915T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./GoldenEye 007 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>GoldenEye 007</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/GoldenEye 007 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>GoldenEye 007 is a 1997 N64 first-person shooter video game developed by Rare and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on August 25, 1997.

You are Bond, James Bond.

You are assigned to covert operations connected with the GoldenEye weapons satellite.  M will brief you on your mission and objectives from London.  Q Branch will support your efforts with a plentiful supply of weapons and gadgets.  Moneypenny offers you light-hearted best wishes and you’re off!

Your mission begins in the heavily guarded chemical warfare facility at the Byelomorye Dam in the USSR.  Look and shoot in any direction as you navigate 12 interactive 3D environments.  Use stealth and force as you see fit in matters of international security.  Consider the military personnel expendable.  You are licensed to kill!

* Exciting 3D environments.
* Highly intelligent enemies!
* Numerous Q gadgets and weapons!
* Battery-backed memory saves game progress!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970825T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Harvest Moon 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Harvest Moon 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Harvest Moon 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Harvest Moon 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Harvest Moon 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Harvest Moon 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Retire to the country for a new challenge in Harvest Moon 64. Hard work is rewarded as you struggle to bring prosperity back to a neglected farm. Work the land, pick up odd-jobs, and get to know the neighbors. Harvest Moon 64 has all the charm of the original Super Nintendo classic, plus many new surprises.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991130T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Toybox</developer>
		<publisher>Natsume</publisher>
		<genre>Construction Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jet Force Gemini (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Jet Force Gemini</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Jet Force Gemini (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Jet Force Gemini (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Jet Force Gemini (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Jet Force Gemini (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The insect invasion has begun.

The galaxy is being infested by the evil Mizar and his horde of Drones. Already, the planet of Goldwood has been subjugated and the peaceful Tribals enslaved. With an arsenal of mega-weapons at their disposal, the Jet Force Gemini team must travel in search of Mizar's lair - rescuing Tribals and splattering Drones along the way. But can Juno, Vela and their faithful dog, Lupus, exterminate the deadly threat before it's too late?</desc>
		<releasedate>19991011T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA).z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Majora's Mask</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Legend of Zelda, The - Majora's Mask (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Link's all-new epic adventure lands him in the mystical world of Termina, where ever-present clocks count down the hours until a menacing moon falls from the sky above. When his horse and Ocarina are stolen by a strange, masked figure, Link embarks on an urgent quest to solve the mystery of the moon, save the world from destruction, and find his way back to the peaceful land of Hyrule.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001026T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA).z64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda - Ocarina of Time</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Golf (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Golf</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Golf (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Golf (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Golf (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Golf (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Forget buying expensive golf gear--Mario brings the game to you. Mario Golf features four complete 18-hole courses, 11 golfers, and precise play control. Create your own golfer and build up his or her experience and skill levels by competing in various tournaments and head-to-head matches. The more you play, the stronger and more accurate your golfer becomes. There are many different modes of play in Mario Golf, including a wide variety of minigames designed to challenge even the most level-headed swingers.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990730T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Camelot Software Planning</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Kart 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Mario Kart 64 is a 1997 N64 racing video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on February 10, 1997.

Three… Two… One… GO! The signal light changes and you drop the pedal to the metal. Take on up to three friends in the split-screen VS games, or race solo in the Mario GP. Tell your friends to bring it on in the highly competitive Battle mode. Advanced features allow you to race with your “Ghost”. The driving data from your best run appears as a transparent character on the screen. No longer must you simply race against the clock -- you can actually race against yourself!

-Save your hottest Ghost data to a portable N64 Controller Pak™ (Sold Separately)

-Collect multiple power-up items!

-Twenty different courses -- 4 Cups with 4 courses each and 4 special Battle mode courses!

-Everyone’s favorite characters are back and gorgeously rendered, including two new additions, Donkey Kong™ and Wario™!</desc>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Party 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Party 2 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Mario and the gang are back for another round of Bowser-bashin' party action! Watch as your favorite Nintendo characters don different duds for each of the five all-new Adventure Boards! A slew of new tricks and devices bring new levels of challenge and excitement to board game play. New board maps, new Mini-Games, new action and new surprises means a whole new batch of fun! Get ready to unleash your best Hip Drops, hammer swings and high-flying high junks for another round of frenzied multi-player action!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>20000124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Strategy, Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party 3 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party 3</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Party 3 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Party 3 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Party 3 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Party 3 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Mario Party 3 is the third and final Mario Party title for the Nintendo 64. A total of eight characters are available to choose from: Mario, Luigi, Princess Peach, Yoshi, Wario, Donkey Kong, and newcomers Waluigi and Princess Daisy. Mario Party 3 features duel maps, in which two players try to lower each other's stamina to zero using non-playable characters such as Chain Chomps. It is the first Mario Party game to feature Luigi's main voice and also it is last Mario game where Princess Daisy appears in a yellow and white dress, and with long hair, as well as the last Mario game (until New Super Mario Bros. Wii) in which Yoshi's "record-scratching" voice is used. It is also the first Mario Party game to have multiple save slots.</desc>
		<releasedate>20010506T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy, Family</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Party (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Party (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Party (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Party (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Every game in the main series has a standard Party Mode in which up to four players play through a board, trying to collect as many stars as possible. In every turn, each player rolls a die and progresses on the board, which usually has branching paths. Coins are primarily earned by performing well in a minigame played at the end of each turn. On most boards, players earn stars by reaching a star space and purchasing a star for a certain amount of coins. The star space appears randomly on one of several pre-determined locations and moves every time a star is purchased, usually occupying a blue space.</desc>
		<releasedate>19990208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy, Family</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Tennis (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Mario Tennis</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Mario Tennis (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mario Tennis (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mario Tennis (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Mario Tennis (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>All of your favorite characters hit the court in a wild and wacky multiplayer tennis game from the makers of Mario Golf. Mario, Luigi, Bowser, Peach, Toad, and Donkey Kong lead off the all-star, 14-player line-up. The fast-paced action will have you unleashing vicious volleys, life-saving lobs, ballistic backhands and electrifying super-charged smashes!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>20000828T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Sports</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Ogre Battle 64 - Person of Lordly Caliber (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Ogre Battle 64 is the third game in the series, the first two being Ogre Battle: The March of the Black Queen, and Tactics Ogre: Let Us Cling Together. The story follows Magnus Gallant, a recent graduate of the Ischka Military Academy, and fledgling captain in Palatinus' Southern region, Alba. As civil war erupts in the country, Magnus eventually decides to join the revolution with its leader, Frederick Raskin, first liberating the southern region with the Zenobians' aid, then Nirdam and uniting with them, then returning the Eastern Region of Capitrium to the Orthodox church, and finally marching on the capital of Latium. However, along the way, Magnus' battalion, the Blue Knights, finds its enemies escalating, from the puppet kingdom of Palatinus, to the might of the Holy Lodis Empire, to the Dark Hordes of the Netherworld.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001007T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Quest</developer>
		<publisher>Atlus Co., Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Paper Mario (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Paper Mario</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Paper Mario (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Paper Mario (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Paper Mario (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Paper Mario (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Paper Mario is a role-playing game developed by Intelligent Systems for the Nintendo 64. It was later re-released for the iQue Player in 2004, the Wii's Virtual Console in 2007, the Wii U's Virtual Console in 2015, and Nintendo 64 - Nintendo Switch Online in 2021.

Paper Mario has the player taking control of Mario on his quest to rescue Princess Peach and save the Mushroom Kingdom from Bowser, who has stolen the mythical Star Rod of Star Haven and used its wish-granting powers to make himself invincible. To stop Bowser and rescue Princess Peach, Mario and company must save the seven Star Spirits; magical beings who have been sealed in cards by Bowser with the power to nullify the Star Rod, as well as the original owners of the Star Rod.

Paper Mario's gameplay is a blend of traditional Japanese role-playing games and Mario-esque platforming features; Mario has the ability to jump in both the overworld and in battle, and jumping remains one of the most important actions in the game. The player controls Mario and a party of followers as they journey through the Mushroom Kingdom, exploring dungeons, managing stats, and battling enemies. The title refers to the game's arts and crafts aesthetic; nearly every character in the game is drawn as a flat 2D sprite, revealing itself as paper-thin when turning around, and many elements of the environments are also depicted as 2D sprites.

Paper Mario was initially in development for the Nintendo 64DD under the name Super Mario RPG 2[5] (also called Mario RPG 2[6] or Mario RPG 64[7]) and intended as a sequel to Super Mario RPG: Legend of the Seven Stars. Concept art posted by Super Mario RPG artist Kazuyuki Kurashima on his Instagram account in 2019 indicated that Samus Aran and Link from the Metroid and The Legend of Zelda franchises would have appeared alongside Mario characters.[8] It later became the first installment of the Paper Mario series and would go on to receive several sequels; the first in the same style of gameplay (Paper Mario: The Thousand-Year Door), followed by four in different playstyles (Super Paper Mario, Paper Mario: Sticker Star, Paper Mario: Color Splash, and Paper Mario: The Origami King).

The above text is from the Super Mario Wiki and is available under a Creative Commons license. Attribution must be provided through a list of authors or a link back to the original article. Source: https://www.mariowiki.com/Paper_Mario</desc>
		<releasedate>20000811T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Intelligent Systems</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Perfect Dark (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Perfect Dark</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Perfect Dark (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Perfect Dark (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Perfect Dark (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Perfect Dark (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Perfect Dark is a 2000 N64 first-person shooter video game developed and released by Rare, under distribution by Nintendo of America, in the USA on May 22, 2000.

Step into the dark... As Carrington Institute's most promising new Agent, Joanna Dark must uncover the truth behind the dataDyne Corporation's recent technological breakthroughs - breakthroughs which could have serious consequences for mankind.

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM) - Secondary Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>20000522T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Rare, Ltd.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Stealth</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Snap (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokemon Snap</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon Snap (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pokemon Snap (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>The Professor has asked you to capture the Wild Pokémon of Pokémon Island… on film!  Tour the island in your ZERO-ONE vehicle and snap pictures of Pokémon in their natural habitat.  Wild Pokémon are often camera-shy, so you’ll have to use special items to bring them out in the open.  Only the best shots will do for the Professor’s Pokémon Report, so sharpen your photography skills and get ready to SNAP!
* The first-ever N64 game to feature the world-famous Pokémon--fully rendered in 3-D!
* Explore the many environments of Pokémon Island, like the sunny beach, the mysterious caves, and even a red-hot volcano!
* Many different types of Pokémon inhabit the island.  See how many you can catch on film!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990321T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter, Life Simulation</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Pokemon Stadium 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Pokemon Stadium 2 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>At long last, all of your favorite Pokémon are rady to go head-to-head on the N64®! Whether you're battle a friend, a Gym Leader or a tournament contestant, you're about to witness some of the most spectacular battle scenes in Pokémon history! Select a team from a huge stable of "rental" battlers, or use the included N64 Transfer Pak™ to upload your own team from Pokémon Red, Blue or Yellow! This Stadium is packed and ready to rock!</desc>
		<releasedate>19990430T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Quest 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Quest 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Quest 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Quest 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Quest 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Quest 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Celtland has been cast into chaos by the theft of Eletale's Book. This mystical volume contains the secrets of the Spirit Tamers. Control Brian, a magician's apprentice, as he explores the expansive countryside and villages on his quest. If he does not reclaim the book, the Kingdom of Celtland will be cast into darkness forever.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980611T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Imagineer</developer>
		<publisher>THQ</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rocket - Robot on Wheels (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Rocket - Robot on Wheels</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Rocket - Robot on Wheels (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>First-time Nintendo 64 developer Sucker Punch Studios jumped onto the scene with a highly original 3D platformer. The design philosophy behind the title is simple -- rather than build the platformer around the main character, the software house opted instead to focus on the interactivity of the 3D environments he travels. To that end, Rocket employs an advanced physics engine which allows the main character, a lovable unicycle-based robot named Rocket, to travel and experiment with colorful, platform-esque worlds with realistic gravity and inertia. Every object has its own set of lifelike attributes that must be "weighed" into consideration when solving puzzles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19991031T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sucker Punch</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Fox 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Fox 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Fox 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Star Fox 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Star Fox 64 (Japanese: スターフォックス64 Hepburn: Sutā Fokkusu Rokujūyon?), known in Australia and Europe as Lylat Wars, is a 3D scrolling shooter game themed around aircraft combat for the Nintendo 64 video game console. It is a reboot of the original Star Fox, and the only game in the Star Fox series to be released on the Nintendo 64. An autostereoscopic remake, titled Star Fox 64 3D, was released for the Nintendo 3DS in 2011.

Star Fox 64 was the first Nintendo 64 game to have included support for the Rumble Pak, with which it initially came bundled. The game received critical acclaim for its smooth animation, detailed visuals, voice acting, and use of multiple gameplay paths.

Star Fox 64 is set on a group of planets in the Lylat system. Ingenious scientist Andross, a native of the fourth planet Corneria, is driven to madness and nearly destroys the planet using biological weapons. For Andross' treason, General Pepper exiles the scientist to the remote planet Venom. Five years after Andross' exile, Pepper detects suspicious activity on Venom.[7] Pepper hires the Star Fox team (consisting of James McCloud, Peppy Hare, and Pigma Dengar) to investigate. When the three arrive at Venom, Pigma betrays the team, which causes James and Peppy to be captured by Andross. Peppy escapes and tells James' son, Fox McCloud, about his father's fate.

A few years later, Andross launches an attack across the Lylat system. Realizing that his army cannot stop Andross, Pepper summons the Star Fox team, now consisting of Fox, Peppy, Falco Lombardi and Slippy Toad.[8] While traveling through several planets, including the Lylat system's star, Solar, and the asteroid field Meteo, the team battles with several of Andross' henchmen, including the rival mercenaries, Star Wolf.

Story:
After arriving in Venom, Fox defeats Andross, but discovers that it is actually a robotic version of himself and destroys it, leaving Andross drifting in the Lylat System. Fox decides to redeem himself by returning to Venom and defeat Star Wolf once again. When Fox defeats Andross once more, he reveals his true form, a floating brain with two floating eyes. After killing Andross, James appears to show Fox the way out, then vanishes immediately after. Escaping the lair's destruction, Star Fox returns to Corneria for a victory celebration, as the game's end credits roll.

When offered membership into the Cornerian Army, Fox declines on behalf of his team; saying "Oh no, sir. We prefer doing things our own way". The game ends with the Great Fox and the Star Fox team flying off in their Arwings into the skies.</desc>
		<releasedate>19970630T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Star Wars Episode I - Battle for Naboo (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Attention defenders of Naboo! The Trade Federation must be stopped! Storm through more than 15 missions over land, sea and space as your freedom fighters rally against the droid armies. Take control of 7 vehicles: the Naboo starfighter, Gian speeder, and new craft like the heavy STAP, Trade Federation gunboat and more. More than 15 missions: escape from Theed, search &amp; destroy, sabotage, reconnaissance, convoy. Battle against Trade Federation droid starfighters, AATs, destroyer droids, battle droids. Change vehicles mid-mission through specially designated hangars.</desc>
		<releasedate>20001218T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Factor 5 GmbH</developer>
		<publisher>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC, Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Star Wars Episode I - Racer</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Star Wars Episode I - Racer (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Join Jedi-to-be Anakin Skywalker in the Star Wars race of your life! Relive all the thrills and excitement of the Podracer sequence from Star Wars: Episode I. Hang on tight - with afterburners on, Podracers max out at a simulated 600 mph! Race in furious competition against more than 21 opponents! Take on over 21 tracks in 8 unique worlds. Avoid hazards such as methane lakes, meteor showers and Tusken Raiders! Featuring spectacular 3D environments!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19990518T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>LucasArts Entertainment Company LLC</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Stunt Racer 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Stunt Racer 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Stunt Racer 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Stunt Racer 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Stunt Racer 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Stunt Racer 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Set in some unspecified time in the future, the gameplay includes more than simple racing. Older vehicles (primarily those regarded even today as classics) are retrofitted with futuristic engine and turbo technology, in addition to jets mounted to allow the car to perform midair stunts. These stunts, including flips, barrel rolls, etc., allow the player to accumulate cash rewards during races on levitating tracks. Money accumulated is used to purchase new cars, as well as upgraded parts for cars (This increases the value of the vehicle. Oddly enough, this feature is relatively useless because vehicles can't be sold.)</desc>
		<releasedate>20001001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Boss Game Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Mario 64 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Super Mario 64</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Mario 64 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Super Mario 64 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Super Mario 64 is a 1996 N64 third-person platformer video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on September 26, 1996.

Mario is super in a whole new way! Combining the finest 3D graphics ever developed for a video game and an explosive soundtrack, Super Mario 64 becomes a new standard for video games. It's packed with bruising battles, daunting obstacle courses and underwater adventures. Retrieve the Power Stars from their hidden locations and confront your arch nemesis -- Bowser, King of the Koopas!

-Run freely in a grassy meadow, tip-toe through a gloomy dungeon, climb to the top of a mountain or take a swim in the moat!

-Leap head first into a watery painting and soon you'll be searching for the surface in an underwater realm!

-On-the-fly, 3D rendered game play delivers the action of ruthless enemy attacks from every angle!

-Find the Caps that give Mario super powers, ponder the mysteries of the pyramid, you can even race Koopas for fabulous prizes!

-With the Nintendo 64 Controller and its analog Control Stick, Mario can crawl, kick down obstacles, swim, do reverse flips, and even stick the landing on his backwards somersault!

-Saved game information is stored for up to four players in memory.</desc>
		<releasedate>19960926T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros. (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Super Smash Bros. (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Super Smash Bros. is a 1999 N64 crossover fighting video game developed by HAL Laboratory and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on April 26, 1999.

It's a Bumpin', Bruisin', Brawlin' Bash!

The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!

-Plunge headlong into battle with your favorite Nintendo characters: Mario, Link, Donkey Kong, Pikachu, Samus, Yoshi, Kirby and Fox... plus 4 hidden characters!

-Characters use their own trademark attacks, such as Mario’s fireballs and Link’s sword.

-Grab a Fire Flower or Poké Ball and send your opponent sailing out of the arena.

-Compete in 8 different settings, each from a character’s home world and each with its own dangers.

• Saves via Internal Memory (SRAM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tigger's Honey Hunt (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Tigger's Honey Hunt</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Tigger's Honey Hunt (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tigger's Honey Hunt (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tigger's Honey Hunt (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Tigger's Honey Hunt (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Winnie the Pooh needs YOU! How can he throw a party without honey? Play as Tigger and run, jump, and bounce around the 100 Acre Wood in search of Pooh's "most favorite" snack. Along the journey there'll be plenty of challenges - blustery blowing leaves to ride, icy terrain, falling boulders, menacing bees, pesky bats and more. Earn Tigger's very special "Tiggertastic Bounce" as a bonus!</desc>
		<releasedate>20001101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Doki Denki Studio</developer>
		<publisher>NewKidCo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Turok 3 - Shadow of Oblivion (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Turok 3: Shadow of Oblivion picks up where Turok 2: Seeds of Evil left off when gamers were first introduced to "Oblivion" and its lackeys, 'Flesh Eaters. Oblivion is a monstrous cosmic entity that consumed everything in its path. It reigned before the birth of our universe. Invading the bodies of the living and devouring them from the inside-out, Oblivion fed on the very energy of the dead and dying. When the Primagen's Lightship was destroyed, the chain reaction it triggered as a result was so powerful that the universe as it existed was completely eradicated, and the almighty Oblivion was pushed to the very brink of destruction. For the first time, Oblivion felt pain, fear, and hate. Though totally ravaged, Oblivion survived and now desperately seeks a means to punch through the Netherscape that separates our world from the Lost Lands (a strange and primitive world where "time has no meaning"), and the Lost Lands from countless others. The last shreds of the pure energy source that created our world and nearly wiped out Oblivion are contained within the Light Burden, the bag that every member of the Turok lineage has carried. The death of the Turok mantle will signal the beginning of the end: the rebirth of Oblivion.

• Saves via Controller Pak</desc>
		<releasedate>20000830T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Acclaim</developer>
		<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Shooter</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Vigilante 8 (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Vigilante 8</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Vigilante 8 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Vigilante 8 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Vigilante 8 (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Vigilante 8 (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Vigilante 8 is a vehicular combat video game developed by Luxoflux and published by Activision for PlayStation, Nintendo 64 and Game Boy Color. It is a spin-off of the Interstate '76 series, featuring several of its theme concepts (auto-vigilantes, the 1970s time frame, and specific fictional vehicle companies).</desc>
		<releasedate>19990317T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Luxoflux Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Activision</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Wave Race 64 - Kawasaki Jet Ski (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Wave Race 64 is sure to provide some of the most exciting racing you've ever experienced. Feel the pounding and crashing of the waves as you accelerate into straight-aways, whip around the marker buoys and go airborne on the jump ramps. Don't race alone! Challenge a friend!</desc>
		<releasedate>19961104T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Xena - Warrior Princess - The Talisman of Fate (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Xena shall choose the defenders of the world. We have seen them in the memories of her exploits. So come together, Earth's greatest heroes and villains. Choose your weapons wisely and let the battles begin! Just remember, each victory only brings you closer to challenging the embodiment of darkness... Despair himself! Each of Xena's 10 characters possess their own unique weapons, attitudes and fighting techniques. Exclusive multi-player feature includes a roster mode, plus team and single battles.</desc>
		<releasedate>19981214T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Saffire Corporation</developer>
		<publisher>Titus Interactive, S.A.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Yoshi's Story (USA).z64</path>
		<name>Yoshi's Story</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Yoshi's Story (USA)</marquee>
		<cartridge>./00Cart/Yoshi's Story (USA)</cartridge>
		<desc>Yoshi's Story is a 1998 N64 side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Nintendo EAD and released by Nintendo of America in the USA on March 10, 1998.

Baby Bowser has taken the Super Happy Tree and cast a spell on Yoshi's world, turning it into the pages of a picture book. The only Yoshies not affected by the spell were six hatchlings that were still protected by their shells. It's up to them to reclaim the Super Happy Tree and restore happiness to the world. That is the only thing that can break Baby Bowser's Spell!

• Saves via Internal Memory (EEPROM)</desc>
		<releasedate>19980310T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
