<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./3rd Birthday, The (USA).iso</path>
		<name>The 3rd Birthday</name>
		<image>./00Image/3rd Birthday, The (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/3rd Birthday, The (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/3rd Birthday, The (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Hideous creatures descend on Manhattan. Ground reports from the squad tasked with containing the pandemonium refer to these life forms as the Twisted. An investigatory team known as the CTI is formed within the year. The Overdive system emerges as a means of opposition, but only one viable candidate exists -- Aya Brea. A gift as she awakens from a lost past on this, the occasion of her third birth.</desc>
		<releasedate>20110329T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hexa Drive</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Archer Maclean's Mercury (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Archer Maclean's Mercury</name>
		<image>./00Image/Archer Maclean's Mercury (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Archer Maclean's Mercury (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Archer Maclean's Mercury (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>From the mind of developer Archer Maclean comes Mercury, a puzzle game that lets you guide the metallic substance through a series of challenging puzzles. Without spilling too much, you must control your colored mercury blobs around 3D mazes simply by tilting the level. Negotiate obstacles and hazards, solve puzzles, and compete against time and percentage limits while avoiding traps and predators. In addition to the single-player mode, Archer Maclean's Mercury also features multiplayer battle and ghost modes.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050406T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Awesome Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Ignition</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Puzzle</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Assassin's Creed - Bloodlines (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Assassin's Creed - Bloodlines</name>
		<image>./00Image/Assassin's Creed - Bloodlines (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Assassin's Creed - Bloodlines (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Assassin's Creed - Bloodlines (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>This is an exclusive PSP entry in the popular Assassin's Creed franchise, which follows covert assassins at crucial junctions in history. This game bridges the story gaps between Assassin's Creed 1 and 2, focusing again on Altair in a storyline set shortly after the events of the first game. Here, the bloodlines that tie these characters are drawn as Altair tracks the remaining Templars to the island of Cyprus.</desc>
		<releasedate>20091117T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Griptonite Games</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Stealth</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles</name>
		<image>./00Image/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castlevania - The Dracula X Chronicles (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The legendary action game Castlevania: Rondo of Blood (the 'lost' chapter never seen before outside of Japan) is reborn on the PSP system with incredible 3D graphics and timeless side scrolling gameplay in Castlevania: The Dracula X Chronicles. Gamers take up the Vampire Killer whip as Richter Belmont as they seek to destroy the maniacal Dracula once and for all in this pivotal piece of the ongoing Castlevania saga. Castlevania: The Dracula X Chronicles also includes unlockable versions of the original Rondo of Blood and Symphony of the Night games, delivering incredible gameplay and value while updating two of the most beloved video games of all time for a new generation of gamers.</desc>
		<releasedate>20071023T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Chili Con Carnage (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Chili Con Carnage</name>
		<image>./00Image/Chili Con Carnage (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Chili Con Carnage (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Chili Con Carnage (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Chili Con Carnage is a semi-sequel to the PS2 game Total Overdose - the Latin-style action game by the same developer. The game recycles a lot of the levels and assets from the PS2 version, but it has new missions and a structure fine-tuned for handheld play. While the original game is a free-roaming GTA clone, the PSP version consists of a series of short missions. It focuses on the shooting sequences of Total Overdose where Ramiro uses his flashiest moves to dispatch mobs and fiends.

The main story mode, El Gringo Loco is identical to Total Overdose. The player takes on the role of Ramiro Cruz, a young man who has just witnessed his dad's murder in classic Mexican fashion «combine harvester through office wall», and now he is on a gun-fueled quest for vengeance through Mexico. The second single player mode El Macho is a collection of different mini challenges which do not tell any story but give access to different characters with different gameplay. The game also future two dynamic multiplayer modes: Hangman for up to 4 players on 1 console and Fiesta for Wi-Fi gameplay.

There is a massive amount of exotic weapons and the gameplay is over the top, with bullet-time and gravity-defying moves.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070227T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Deadline Games A/S</developer>
		<publisher>Eidos Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dante's Inferno (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Dante's Inferno</name>
		<image>./00Image/Dante's Inferno (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Dante's Inferno (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Dante's Inferno (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Dante's Inferno will take gamers to the western world's most definitive view of the afterlife as created by the 13th century Italian poet Dante Alighieri. Each of the nine circles will showcase its own distinct look, with demons, monsters and geography that are crafted straight from the poem's vivid descriptions. Using Death's Scythe and Beatrice's Holy Cross, and a slate of magic powers with a deep, customizable upgrade system, players will experience a fast and fluid 60 frames-per-second gameplay experience.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100301T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>EA Redwood Shores</developer>
		<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Daxter (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Daxter</name>
		<image>./00Image/Daxter (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Daxter (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Daxter (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Daxter is centered around the world of the lovable orange ottsel made popular in the Jak and Daxter franchise. The story unfolds as Daxter searches for Jak, who was imprisoned during the events that led to the start of "Jak II." Daxter, now on his own in an unfamiliar place, quickly realizes that being small and furry won't help his chances of survival. To help stamp out a mysterious metalbug infestation, Daxter takes on a job as a pest exterminator, enabling him to explore parts of Haven City in an effort to collect the clues that will lead him to Jak. Daxter allows gamers to play from his perspective offering a distinctive set of moves with agile abilities that allows players to climb walls, creep up on enemies, fit in small places and maneuver vehicles. Taking a job as a pest exterminator, to fight an ongoing invasion of metal-bugs, Daxter comes equip with gadgets to rid the city of these metal nuisances. Get close up and personal by using your flimsy bug swatter to squash an army of attacking insects or your spray gun to hover around a variety of environments while picking up various upgrades.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War - Chains of Olympus (USA).iso</path>
		<name>God of War - Chains of Olympus</name>
		<image>./00Image/God of War - Chains of Olympus (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/God of War - Chains of Olympus (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/God of War - Chains of Olympus (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The game is set in Ancient Greece and loosely based on its mythology. The player controls Kratos, a Spartan warrior in the service of the Olympian Gods. Kratos is guided by the goddess Athena, who instructs him to find the Sun God Helios, as the Dream God Morpheus has caused the remaining gods to slumber in Helios' absence. With the power of the sun, Morpheus and Persephone, the Queen of the Underworld, with the aid of the Titan Atlas, intend to destroy the Pillar of the World and in turn Olympus. God of War: Chains of Olympus is chronologically the second chapter in the series, which focuses on vengeance as its central theme.</desc>
		<releasedate>20080304T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ready at Dawn</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Fighting</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./God of War - Ghost of Sparta (USA).iso</path>
		<name>God of War - Ghost of Sparta</name>
		<image>./00Image/God of War - Ghost of Sparta (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/God of War - Ghost of Sparta (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/God of War - Ghost of Sparta (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The next installment of the series for Sony's portable console contains all the characteristic elements of God of War, i.e. battles with powerful bosses, an advanced combat system, an epic plot referring to Greek mythology and great visuals. In the game, we again play the role of the powerful Spartan Kratos, who hates the Greek gods.

The plot of Ghost of Sparta takes place immediately after the end of the first installment of the series, in which Kratos killed Ares and ascended to Olympus as the new god of war. It turns out that the hero's new powers may not be enough to stop the nightmares from his past. To deal with his dark history, the brutal warrior must set off on a new journey.

Kratos couldn't do without new combat capabilities. In Ghost of Sparta, of course, the hero uses Athena's characteristic blades and many other weapons. What is new is the ability to perform a charge, during which the warrior catches the opponent and throws him against the wall. Kratos' repertoire has been enriched with air strikes, new animations for killing enemies and several other elements (e.g. spear and shield). Of course, the system of collecting energy and experience points and developing the character also returns. In some locations we also have to solve simple riddles and puzzles.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100211T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Santa Monica Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Interactive Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - Chinatown Wars (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>LEFT FOR DEAD IN THE WORST PLACE IN AMERICA

Following his father's murder, Huang Lee has a simple mission: deliver an ancient sword to his Uncle Kenny to ensure his family retains control of the Triad gangs of Liberty City. Huang is a spoiled rich kid who expects everything to run smoothly, but his trip does not go exactly as planned. After being robbed and left to die, he will search for honor, riches and revenge in the most dangerous and morally bankrupt city in the world.</desc>
		<releasedate>20091020T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar Leeds, Rockstar North</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Sandbox</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Grand Theft Auto - Sindacco Chronicles.iso</path>
		<name>Grand Theft Auto - Sindacco Chronicles</name>
		<image>./00Image/Grand Theft Auto - Sindacco Chronicles</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Grand Theft Auto - Sindacco Chronicles</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Grand Theft Auto - Sindacco Chronicles</marquee>
		<desc>1998. A new Mafia war is on the rise in Liberty City – the Sindacco, Forelli and Leone families are at their throats again for domination over the worst city in America. The Sindaccos, led by the ambitious Paulie Sindacco, plan to conquer what they can before the others can get their hands on what’s left of the city. A loyal henchman they have, Joseph Daniel O’Toole, is supposed to infiltrate the Leone Family. Meanwhile, Paulie’s two nephews, Frank and Marcus, are preparing their men for a big war…</desc>
		<releasedate>20230608T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Barcode Studia</developer>
		<publisher>Homebrew</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Sandbox, Unofficial</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gran Turismo (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Gran Turismo</name>
		<image>./00Image/Gran Turismo (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Gran Turismo (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Gran Turismo (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The game is centered on an open-ended design. The single-player menu presents players with three variables — Mode Selection (Time Trial, Single Race, and Drift Trial), Car Selection, and Track Selection. The player can pick and choose circuits and vehicles, with credits earned based on the difficulty, performance and number of laps they have chosen. Players can select from any number of laps, one to 99. There are 45 tracks (including layout variations) plus the added bonus of reverse on most tracks, which takes the track number close to 75. For the first time in the series, the game features the use of custom soundtracks that enables players to play their own songs while racing, but this option must first be unlocked by completing section B of the Driving Challenges. The music tracks can only be played if it is set on "MUSIC folder" and can be used for offline or online races.</desc>
		<releasedate>20091001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Polyphony Digital Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Gurumin - A Monstrous Adventure (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Gurumin - A Monstrous Adventure</name>
		<image>./00Image/Gurumin - A Monstrous Adventure (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Gurumin - A Monstrous Adventure (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Gurumin - A Monstrous Adventure (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Gurumin: A Monstrous Adventure is a fantastic Action-RPG from leading Japanese developer Falcom (Developers of “Ys” and “Zwei” among other classics) featuring real-time combat, stunning 3D graphics, tons of fully voiced characters and mini-games , 90+ items, multiple endings, a rocking soundtrack, 35+ hours of playtime, and more.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070212T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nihon Falcom Corp.</developer>
		<publisher>Mastiff, LLC</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Jeanne d'Arc (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Jeanne d'Arc</name>
		<image>./00Image/Jeanne d'Arc (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Jeanne d'Arc (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Jeanne d'Arc (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>In the past, there was a great war between humans and demons. Five heroes created five magical armlets and used their combined power to seal the demons away. Much time has passed, and now France and England are in the midst of the Hundred Years' War. Domrémy, a small village in the Lorraine region of France, was celebrating a festival when suddenly English soldiers attacked. A village girl, Jeanne, was led by a voice from the heavens to save France. Thus begins the journey of Jeanne, and her friends Roger and Liane, in the war to free their country from the tyranny of the demon-controlled English army.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070821T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Level-5</developer>
		<publisher>Sony</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./LocoRoco (USA).iso</path>
		<name>LocoRoco</name>
		<image>./00Image/LocoRoco (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/LocoRoco (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/LocoRoco (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>LocoRoco is a 2006 PlayStation Portable side-scrolling puzzle platformer video game developed by Japan Studio and released by Sony Computer Entertainment America in the USA on September 5, 2006.

LocoRoco is an innovative 2D platform/action game available exclusively for the PSP. Featuring unique controls utilizing the "L" and "R" shoulder buttons, players are tasked with controlling via "tilting or bumping" the landscape of the LocoRoco in order to help them navigate through the level and keep them out of harm's way. With more than 40 stages, players control and guide the LocoRoco through vibrant, thriving and lush worlds filled with slippery slopes, swing ropes , and more. Featuring six different types of LocoRoco that include their own voices and actions, players will be enchanted by captivating music that communicates the joyous world of these LocoRoco. In addition, LocoRoco features the rewarding LocoHouse, three mini-games , and wireless features. The peaceful world of the LocoRoco are under attack by the not-so-nice Moja Corps. These evil outer space creatures want nothing but to capture the blissful LocoRoco and take them from their land of blowing flowers, lively creatures and pastel scenery. As the planet where the LocoRoco inhabit, players must tilt, roll and bounce the LocoRoco to safety.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060905T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lunar - Silver Star Harmony (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Lunar - Silver Star Harmony</name>
		<image>./00Image/Lunar - Silver Star Harmony (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lunar - Silver Star Harmony (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lunar - Silver Star Harmony (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>While seemingly placid on the surface, the world of Lunar is slowly descending into chaos, as the Goddess Althena, the creator and guardian of the world, has disappeared and the valiant efforts of the legendary Dragonmaster Dyne and his faithful companions fade into obscurity. With Althena gone and no one able or willing to become the next Dragonmaster, a shadowy figure, known only as the Magic Emperor, has started plotting to usurp Althena's place and become a god. In a remote village far removed from the decay that is slowly spreading throughout the world lives a young man named Alex, who dreams of one day becoming the next Dragonmaster like his hero Dyne. One day, Alex's friend Ramus convinces him to head towards a cave near town, where it is rumored the legendary White Dragon resides. With Alex's adopted sister Luna and his mysterious pet Nall in tow, Alex heads off on what seems to be a meaningless adventure, not knowing that it would be the first step in an epic journey with the fate of the entire world at stake.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100302T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Game Arts</developer>
		<publisher>XSEED Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mega Man - Powered Up (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mega Man - Powered Up</name>
		<image>./00Image/Mega Man - Powered Up (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mega Man - Powered Up (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mega Man - Powered Up (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Mega Man ...like you've never seen him!

The diabolical Dr. Wily is bent on world domination, and only Mega Man can stop his evil Minions. With a spiffy new look and amazing new powers, Mega Man is better than ever in his wildest adventure yet!

For the first time ever, play as any of the powerful bosses! Take control! Build &amp; explore your own levels. Use Infrastructure Mode to send your creations to Mega Man users around the world and test their skill.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060314T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Metal Gear Ac!d (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Metal Gear Ac!d</name>
		<image>./00Image/Metal Gear Ac!d (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Metal Gear Ac!d (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Metal Gear Ac!d (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The Metal Gear series comes to the PSP offering a new gameplay system and storyline. In Metal Gear Acid, you'll take on the role of Solid Snake, a top-secret agent who's an expert at infiltration. It's up to you to make calculated decisions to plan out your strategy and accomplish missions in a turn-based style of game. Strategic battle cards give you different abilities and stealth tactics that help you achieve mission objectives. Experience a deeper kind of tactical espionage in the palm of your hand.</desc>
		<releasedate>20050324T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami Computer Entertainment Japan</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Strategy, Stealth</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Midnight Club - LA Remix (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Midnight Club - LA Remix</name>
		<image>./00Image/Midnight Club - LA Remix (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Midnight Club - LA Remix (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Midnight Club - LA Remix (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Race at breakneck speeds through the streets of modern-day L.A. in Midnight Club L.A. Remix, the ultimate racing experience for the PSP.  Drive the hottest real-world tuners, muscle and luxury cars, exotics and superbikes on the streets today.  Customize your vehicle with the best after-market performance parts and custom kits.  And exclusive to Midnight Club L.A. Remix, travel to Tokyo to test your skills against the best racers in the world.  Street racing with no track and no rules: Welcome to the Midnight Club</desc>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rockstar London</developer>
		<publisher>Rockstar Games</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mortal Kombat - Unchained (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Mortal Kombat - Unchained</name>
		<image>./00Image/Mortal Kombat - Unchained (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Mortal Kombat - Unchained (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Mortal Kombat - Unchained (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>It will konsume you!

An ancient evil has returned from beyond death and threatens the very existence of the realms. Will the Champion of the Elder Gods have the power to defeat this threat borne of deception?

-Features six additional fighters including Kitana, Jax, Frost, Blaze, Goro and Shao Kahn,
-Battle your way to the top in the all-new Endurance Mode.
-Multiple fatalities, hara karis and interactive multi-tiered backrounds including brutal death traps.
-Explore the huge free-roaming adventure in Konquest Mode.
-Engage in Chess and Puzzle Kombat...MK style.
-Fight head-to-head against a friend with Wi-Fi wireless support.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061115T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>JGI Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Midway Games</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Patapon 2 (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Patapon 2</name>
		<image>./00Image/Patapon 2 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Patapon 2 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Patapon 2 (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The story of the Patapon tribe marches forth as they hunt for the fabled Earthend. Shipwrecked in a new and strange continent the Patapon are depending on you, their god, to lead them safely through this perilous new land. As you guide the tribe through this new world with your mystical drum, they will come face to face with a new tribe, encounter a mysterious and mighty Hero Patapon and uncover the ruins of Patapolis, a mystical place long spoken of by the Patapon. All-new modes to Patapon 2 include thrilling multiplayer stages, a huge array of missions and deep tutorials that will have you drumming to the beat of the Patapon in no time. Head to patapon-game.com for the captivating mini-game, The Art Of War, where the goal is to collect as many Patapon characters as you can and then immortalise your battle with the Patapon Wallpaper creator. Lead your loyal followers through 60 rhythmic stages. Keep the beat going with tons of hidden items and mini-games to reveal. Drum along with friends and tackle multiplayer missions.</desc>
		<releasedate>20090505T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sony Japan Studio</developer>
		<publisher>SCEI</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Strategy, Music</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ratchet & Clank - Size Matters (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Ratchet & Clank - Size Matters</name>
		<image>./00Image/Ratchet & Clank - Size Matters (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ratchet & Clank - Size Matters (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ratchet & Clank - Size Matters (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>While on a much needed vacation, Ratchet and Clank's rest and relaxation time is suddenly cut short as they soon find themselves lured into a mysterious quest. Following the trail of a kidnapped girl, Ratchet and Clank rediscover a forgotten race of genius inventors known as the Technomites. They soon uncover a plot more dangerous than they could have imagined. Featuring new and returning weapons and gadgets, including the Shocker, Agents of Doom and Shrink Ray, Ratchet &amp; Clank: Size Matters packs all of the combat and destruction fans have come to expect from the series.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070213T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>High Impact Games</developer>
		<publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Shooter, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sid Meier's Pirates! (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sid Meier's Pirates!</name>
		<image>./00Image/Sid Meier's Pirates! (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sid Meier's Pirates! (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sid Meier's Pirates! (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>In Sid Meier's Pirates!, a strategy/adventure game, players take the role of a Pirate Captain in the 17th century Caribbean - amassing fortune and fame in an attempt to seize a rightful place as one of the most revered and feared pirates in history. Players test their skills as a sea captain exploring the high seas and dueling in land and sea battles in a richly detailed 3D world. Additional features for the PSP system include wireless Ad-Hoc multiplayer for up to four players, widescreen graphics, new treasure hunts and more.</desc>
		<releasedate>20070122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Full Fat Games</developer>
		<publisher>2K Games</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure, Strategy</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic Rivals (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Sonic Rivals</name>
		<image>./00Image/Sonic Rivals (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sonic Rivals (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sonic Rivals (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The game begins with Doctor Eggman turning Tails, Amy Rose, Rouge, and the Master Emerald into cards with his new device. Sonic and Knuckles arrive on the scene, and find out what has happened. Knuckles, bent on saving the Master Emerald, tells Sonic that teamwork is out of the question and that he needs to get to Eggman first. Sonic snickers and says that he likes a good challenge.

Meanwhile, Shadow the Hedgehog receives a distress signal from Eggman. Suddenly, a mysterious hedgehog named Silver appears from the future. Silver is then pursued by Shadow. When they encounter each other, Silver tells Shadow he needs to get to Eggman, first. After numerous conflicts, it is revealed that Dr. Eggman is in fact Eggman Nega and that the real Doctor Eggman is captured into a card prior to the story. After one final battle with Sonic, Knuckles, Shadow and Silver, Nega is defeated, everyone is reverted to their original forms, and Silver returns to the future with Eggman Nega who is trapped inside a card.</desc>
		<releasedate>20061116T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Backbone Vancouver</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Racing, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Star Ocean - First Departure (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Star Ocean - First Departure</name>
		<image>./00Image/Star Ocean - First Departure (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Star Ocean - First Departure (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Star Ocean - First Departure (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Star Ocean games are known for their real-time battle engines, and, for being one of the first of its kind to come to the consoles. Battles take place on a separate screen, but all characters (rather than waiting in one spot and taking damage) are fully mobile in three dimensions, can dodge and chase foes, and must cast their spells and deploy attacks despite enemy harassment. In the earlier games, magicians had spells, whereas fighters had special physical attacks called "Killer Moves"; both are learned after passing certain level requirements (or through specific items and sidequests) and cost HP or MP to use. In Star Ocean: Till the End of Time, all the characters are able to use spells and battle skills (i.e. killer moves).</desc>
		<releasedate>20081021T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>tri-Ace</developer>
		<publisher>Square Enix</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Tekken - Dark Resurrection</name>
		<image>./00Image/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Tekken - Dark Resurrection (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The power of the greatest fighting dynasty... in the pal of your hands.

Tekken: Dark Resurrection has arrived on the PSP system. Fight with new characters Lili and Dragunov or other favorites including Jin, Heihachi, and Armor King.

-Wireless ad hoc battle with up to 2 players to prove who is the real champion.
-Customize your character with twice the items and share your creation using the Ghost feature.
-Play mini-games in ad hoc mode or individually for a change in the action.
-Stunning graphics on 19 stages of pain.</desc>
		<releasedate>20060725T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Bandai Namco Entertainment</developer>
		<publisher>Bandai Namco Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ys Seven (USA).iso</path>
		<name>Ys Seven</name>
		<image>./00Image/Ys Seven (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ys Seven (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ys Seven (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>The kingdom of Altago is rebuilding their kingdom around a newfound peace after years of war against the merciless armies of Romn. The classic adventuresome duo, Adol and Dogi, arrive in the harbor of Altago City, and quickly find themselves in a scuffle with the Dragon Knights, the kingdom's military police body, when attempting to save a local girl from harassment by one of their commanding officers. Upset by the interruption and subsequent humiliation, the commander arrests Adol and Dogi, charging them with espionage. 

The king of Altago, having known of the duo's pending arrival from an old trusted friend, quickly releases the pair from prison and summons them to his chambers. He tells the men about an ancient shrine that was uncovered after a recent earthquake, and asks for their help in investigating this mysterious new find. Adol and Dogi oblige, unaware that they are about to take the first steps on a long journey to save all of Altago from long-forgotten ancient forces, and to reunite the estranged five tribes who serve and protect the Five Great Dragons deified beings who may well be the world's last hope. 

Ys Seven is the latest installment in the long-running Ys series which first debuted on PC in 1987. This is the first iteration to be built specifically for the PSP system, taking full advantage of the widescreen format and hardware. The battle system consists of a three-member battle party with enemies engaged on the field map in real-time for fast-paced combat. Old fans of the series and new players alike will be immersed into the rich vibrant world containing over 30 hours of gameplay.</desc>
		<releasedate>20100817T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Falcom</developer>
		<publisher>XSEED Games</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
