<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Aladdin (USA).md</path>
		<name>Aladdin</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Aladdin (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Aladdin (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Aladdin (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Hang onto your carpet for ACTION and FUN! Aladdin slashes his shining scimitar to fight through Agrabah, escape the Sultan's dungeon, survive the fiery Cave of Wonders, snatch the Genie's Lamp and save Princess Jasmine from the evil Jafar! All-new technology creates animation so smooth, it's like watching a real animated film. Aladdin battles thieves and desert warriors, and barely dodges danger on his high-speed carpet. Survive Jafar's troops for a dash through special bonus rounds. Hilarious! Palace Guards drop their drawers and camels spit dirt wads. Aladdin ping-pongs like a pinball INSIDE the Genie's Lamp!</desc>
		<releasedate>19931111T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Software, Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Altered Beast (USA, Europe).md</path>
		<name>Altered Beast</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Altered Beast (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Altered Beast (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Altered Beast (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Altered Beast is a 1989 Genesis side-scrolling beat 'em up platformer video game developed by Sega R&amp;D2 and released by Sega of America in the USA on August 14, 1989.

The player is in control of a centurion who had died in battle. The centurion has been raised from the dead to rescue Zeus' daughter Athena from the demon Neff. The player battles undead and demonic hordes, controlling the shapeshifting hero. He must fight through several levels in order to save the kidnapped goddess. Although 'Centurion' was a rank in the Roman Army, the game takes place in a setting resembling Ancient Greece, complete with gods, temples and ruined Ionic columns.</desc>
		<releasedate>19890814T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega R&amp;D2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting, Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ariel - The Little Mermaid (USA, Europe).md</path>
		<name>Ariel - The Little Mermaid</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Ariel - The Little Mermaid (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ariel - The Little Mermaid (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ariel - The Little Mermaid (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>King Triton and his daughter Ariel battle the dangers of the deep to save the kingdom. As Triton, you must rescue Ariel and break Ursula's curse. As Ariel, the little mermaid, you must battle bewitched sea creatures and defeat Ursula to save Triton and the kidnapped merpeople. Dodge angry sharks, sword-wielding skeletons, and falling boulders. Battle the Molten Lava monster and slimy, stinging eels. And if you dare, brave the snake-infested locks of The Medusa. Navigate through undersea mazes, avoiding traps. Pals Sebastian and Flounder rush to the rescue in tight spots. Open sunken treasure chests loaded with booty. Consult maps which lead to your imprisoned friends. Then come face to face with Ursula the Sea Witch, and battle her in a final showdown!</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>BlueSky Software</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Beauty and the Beast - Roar of the Beast (USA).md</path>
		<name>Beauty and the Beast - Roar of the Beast</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Beauty and the Beast - Roar of the Beast (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Beauty and the Beast - Roar of the Beast (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Beauty and the Beast - Roar of the Beast (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>As the Beast, the player must successfully complete several levels, based on scenes from the film, in order to protect the castle from invading villagers and forest animals and rescue Belle from the evil Gaston.</desc>
		<releasedate>19931001T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sunsoft</developer>
		<publisher>SUNSOFT</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe).md</path>
		<name>Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castle of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Each level exists within the large titular castle and the player must defeat enemies and bosses by jumping on them, or collecting apples and marbles to use as projectiles. The player can also collect icons to increase health, collect extra lives, or gain bonus points. After defeating a boss, the player is given a gem. When all seven gems are collected, the player can build a rainbow bridge that allows him/her to walk into the castle's tower for a final battle against the witch (who in her youthful form resembles the Queen Grimhilde).</desc>
		<releasedate>19901121T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA).md</path>
		<name>Castlevania - Bloodlines</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Castlevania - Bloodlines (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Castlevania: Bloodlines, known as Vampire Killer in Japan and as Castlevania: The New Generation in PAL regions, is a platform game developed and published by Konami for the Sega Genesis, released worldwide in March 1994. It was the only Castlevania video game released on the Genesis.
The game's storyline concerns a legendary vampire named Elizabeth Bartley who is Dracula's niece, suddenly appearing in the 20th century. Plotting a sacrificial war in order to bring her uncle back to life, she orchestrates the beginning of World War I. Quincy Morris' son, John, and his best friend Eric Lecarde, vow to take up the fight against evil. Together they manage to prevent Dracula's full resurrection.
Unlike most Castlevania games, Bloodlines was the first game in the series that does not take place exclusively in Dracula's castle, with most levels taking place throughout Europe.</desc>
		<releasedate>19940318T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Konami</developer>
		<publisher>Konami</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun (USA, Europe).md</path>
		<name>Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Dungeons & Dragons - Warriors of the Eternal Sun (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Dungeon &amp; Dragons: Warriors of the Eternal Sun is set in the world of Mystara, a setting of the Dungeons &amp; Dragons game. The characters find themselves in a strange, red-hued world in which the horizon slopes upward in all directions, eventually vanishing into a crimson haze at the limits of sight. Their mission is to find and make allies in this new world or else the kingdom and its culture will perish.

The player leads a party of four characters (either the default party or one that the player has created). Characters and races can be chosen from the normal D&amp;D options. The gameworld is viewed from an isometric perspective and the characters can roam around in realtime. Battles are turn based. Like most role-playing games, the gaming experience focuses on exploration, inventory management and character development.</desc>
		<releasedate>19920101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Westwood Studios, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe, Korea).md</path>
		<name>Ecco the Dolphin</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe, Korea)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe, Korea)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Ecco the Dolphin (USA, Europe, Korea)</marquee>
		<desc>Ecco the Dolphin is a 1992 Genesis side-scrolling action-adventure video game developed by Novotrade and released by Sega of America in the USA on December 29, 1992.

Travel through time along with Ecco the dolphin, in the only game that could call itself a "dolphin simulator". Indeed, you can do pretty much everything a typical dolphin does, including eating fish, surfacing in order to breathe, using your biological sonar and of course, jumping out of the water to amaze your friends.

The storyline is actually deeper that one may think by looking at the box illustration. As Ecco, you are the only dolphin who managed to escape from a giant whirlpool which sucked down your entire pod. The five shining stars on your forehead show that you are the chosen one to save them. But that task will be not be an easy one, as you will have to travel through time and space with the Atlantean time machine, and meet the mystical Asterite in order to defeat the Vortex Queen.

The main part of the gameplay in Ecco the Dolphin relies on exploring various aquatic levels. They are usually nonlinear, with submerged caverns and tunnels branching out from the main bodies of water. The navigation is impeded by islands that must be hopped over, volcanoes that spit hot lava, powerful currents, deadly spikes, and dangerous predators such as octopi and giant eels. The sonar ability has multiple functions: you can communicate with friendly animals, map out the nearby area (echolocation), activate glyphs, and eventually defeat enemies. Activating glyphs is necessary because they can unlock unexplored parts of the current level, including the exit that leads to the next area; some of them can even bestow the gift of invincibility on Ecco for a limited time.

You must keep an eye on the life and breath meters. Dolphins can't stay underwater for a long period of time and must return to the surface for air. However, the cavern systems may hide the occasional pocket of air as well. Every time you are hit by spikes, lava, or an enemy, Ecco loses health, and once it reaches zero you will have to replay the level from the beginning. The life meter can be replenished by eating fish or by finding healing clams, called the Shelled Ones, and communicating with them. It's possible to avoid most enemies, but Ecco can kill troublesome creatures using the death sonar or by charging them head-on.</desc>
		<releasedate>19921229T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Novotrade International</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>kr,en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Golden Axe II (World).md</path>
		<name>Golden Axe II</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Golden Axe II (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Golden Axe II (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Golden Axe II (World)</marquee>
		<desc>Golden Axe II is a 1991 Genesis side-scrolling hack and slash beat 'em up video game developed by Sega CS and released by Sega of America in the USA on December 24, 1991.

Not long after the malign reign of the Death Adder has ended, another evil rises. The peace of the land has again been threatened, this time by 'Dark Guld', who was supposed to be imprisoned but apparently isn't. He has instead now got his hands on the Golden Axe, and is using it for his own nasty purposes, and with his minions is causing much chaos.

So once more, Ax-Battler, the fierce barbarian; Tyris-Flare, the fearless Amazon; Gilius Thunderhead, the ferocious dwarf; get up to deal with the oppression, with their might and magic, and recover the Golden Axe.

The hack and slash gameplay, in a medieval fantasy setting, is essentially the same to that of the previous game. Beat up opponents with melee attacks and collect scrolls to launch magical attacks. Moreover, players can also ride dragons and other beasts and use their attack capabilities to their advantage.</desc>
		<releasedate>19911224T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega CS R&amp;D 2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The 3.md</path>
		<name>The Lion King 3</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The 3</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The 3</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The 3</marquee>
		<desc>Lion King 3 is a platform game released for the Sega Mega Drive based, not the Disney film of the same name, but the original film itself, as a follow-up to the Mega Drive game The Lion King II. It was developed by an unknown company likely connected to Gamtec and published by X Boy.</desc>
		<releasedate>19980101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamtec</developer>
		<publisher>X Boy, Romhacking, Unlicenced</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The II.md</path>
		<name>The Lion King II</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The II</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The II</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The II</marquee>
		<desc>The Lion King II is an unlicensed platformer for the Sega Mega Drive. It is loosely based on the 1994 film The Lion King (as opposed to its 1998 sequel which shares The Lion King II title). It was developed by Gamtec at an unknown date, and uses sound effects from Wonder Boy III: Monster Lair.</desc>
		<releasedate>19950101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Gamtec</developer>
		<publisher>Romhacking, Unlicenced</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Lion King, The (World).md</path>
		<name>The Lion King</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Lion King, The (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Lion King, The (World)</marquee>
		<desc>The Lion King is a 1994 Genesis side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Westwood Studios (co-developed by Krisalis Software) and released by Virgin Interactive Entertainment Inc. and Disney Software in the USA on November 9, 1994.

It is based on the movie, The Lion King, which was produced by Walt Disney Feature Animation and released in theaters on June 15, 1994.

You think you want to be King? Get real. You're starting life as Simba, the cub. To survive and grow into a powerful adult lion, you must perfect your savage pounce, reckless roar, and master fighting with all four paws. If you survive the challenge, you'll grow into a strong, ferocious adult lion. So prepare to scrap with hyenas. Blast through an elephant graveyard. Battle an in-your-face stampede of trampling wildebeests. And you'd better quit hanging with slackers like Timon and Pumbaa, unless you want to be scarfing bugs the rest of your life! Are you sure you want to be King? Then it's time to cut loose in the deadliest one-on-one brawl ever. Defeat your evil Uncle Scar. Recapture the Pridelands. And reclaim your rightful place in the Circle of Life.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941109T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Krisalis Software Ltd., Westwood Studios</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Software, Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure (USA).md</path>
		<name>McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>McDonald's Treasure Land Adventure is a side-scrolling adventure starring Ronald McDonald.

After finding a piece of a treasure map, the yellow clown travels through four different levels (Forest, Town, Sea and Moon). He's off to find and defeat the baddies who have the other pieces of the map.

Ronald can jump, shoot and use his scarf to grab onto hooks to jump to higher levels.

Jewels and flowers collected in each level can be used to purchase extra lives and power-ups in shops between levels.</desc>
		<releasedate>19930923T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Treasure</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Phantasy Star IV (USA).md</path>
		<name>Phantasy Star IV</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Phantasy Star IV (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Phantasy Star IV (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Phantasy Star IV (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Phantasy Star IV is a 1995 Genesis role-playing video game developed by Sega CS and released by Sega of America in the USA on February 1, 1995.

Launch into the biggest RPG ever on Genesis! This is the explosive magic-and-monster packed FINALE to the incredible Phantasy Star saga. An ancient, hideous Dark Force stalks the Algol star system. You, a young hunter, are destined to become Motavia's greatest warrior and strike the death-blow that destroys evil FOREVER!</desc>
		<releasedate>19950201T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega CS R&amp;D 2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Role-Playing</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Pocahontas (USA).md</path>
		<name>Pocahontas</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Pocahontas (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Pocahontas (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Pocahontas (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>Incarnation of the Disney cartoon; Pocahontas, along with a tag team partner in her raccoon friend, Meeko, goes about her homeland, helping her animal friends. As so is done, she will acquire animal spirits which will help her become stronger and bless her with new abilities.

But soon enough she meets John Smith, and as an inevitable consequence has to prevent a war between his and John's people. And she has to do it in a hurry, before John's neck gets a non-"disney" treatment..</desc>
		<releasedate>19960101T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Funcom</developer>
		<publisher>Disney Interactive</publisher>
		<genre>Action</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3 (USA).md</path>
		<name>Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3 (USA)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3 (USA)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sonic & Knuckles + Sonic The Hedgehog 3 (USA)</marquee>
		<desc>'Sonic &amp; Knuckles' is locked-on to the original Sonic the Hedgehog or Sonic Compilation via Lock-On Technology, the result is a deceptive "No Way!" screen. However, by pressing the A, B and C buttons together players can access Special Stage levels, commonly known as the "Blue Sphere" levels. Levels can be accessed by inputting a twelve digit code, every number combination a different variation of a Special Stage level.</desc>
		<releasedate>19941018T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World).md</path>
		<name>Sonic The Hedgehog 2</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sonic The Hedgehog 2 (World)</marquee>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog 2 is a 1992 Genesis side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Sonic Team (co-developed by Sega Technical Institute) and released by Sega of America in the USA on November 24, 1992.

Super Speed! Sonic's back and better than ever. He's a blur in blue! A blaze of action! With his new Super Spin Dash. And a new, fabulous friend, "Tails" the Fox. You won't believe it 'til you see it. And when you play, you won't stop. Super Play! Defy gravity in hair-raising loop-de-loops. Grab Power Sneakers and race like lightning through the mazes. Dash in a dizzying whirl across corkscrew speedway. Bounce like a pinball through the bumpers and springs of the amazing Zones. All at break-neck speed! Super Power! Sonic's attitude is can-do. The mad scientist Dr. Robotnik is planning a world takeover. Sonic gets tough in the fight to save his friends and squash Robotnik for good!</desc>
		<releasedate>19921124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega Technical Institute, Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe).md</path>
		<name>Sonic The Hedgehog</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Sonic The Hedgehog (USA, Europe)</marquee>
		<desc>Sonic the Hedgehog is a 1991 Genesis side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Sonic Team and released by Sega of America in the USA on June 23, 1991.

Super Speed! Bust the video game speed barrier wide open with Sonic the Hedgehog. Blaze by in a blur using the super sonic spin attack. Loop the loop by defying gravity. Plummet down tunnels. Then dash to safety with Sonic's power sneakers. All at a frenzied pace. Super Graphics! Help Sonic escape bubbling molten lava. Swim through turbulent waterfalls. Scale glistening green mountains. And soar past shimmering city lights. There's even a 360 degree rotating maze. You've never seen anything like it. Supper Attitude! Sonic has an attitude that just won't quit. He's flip and funny, yet tough as nails as he fights to free his friends from evil. So just wait. Sonic may be the world's next SUPER hero...</desc>
		<releasedate>19910623T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sonic Team</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>1</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (E).md</path>
		<name>Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (E)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (E)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/Street Fighter II' - Special Champion Edition (E)</marquee>
		<desc>Street Fighter II': Special Champion Edition is a 1993 Genesis fighting video game developed by Capcom and released by Capcom USA in the USA on September 27, 1993.

From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Vega's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as M. Bison, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</desc>
		<releasedate>19930927T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom USA, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Fighting</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>en</lang>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck (USA, Korea).md</path>
		<name>World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck</name>
		<image>./00Boxart/World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck (USA, Korea)</image>
		<thumbnail>./00Boxart/World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck (USA, Korea)</thumbnail>
		<marquee>./00Logo/World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck (USA, Korea)</marquee>
		<desc>World of Illusion Starring Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck is a 1992 Genesis side-scrolling platformer video game developed by Sega CS and released by Sega of America in the USA on December 17, 1992.

Alakazam! Here's classic Disney fun with your favorites, Mickey Mouse and Donald Duck! Transported into a world of wonder, Mickey and Donald must perform amazing feats of magic to defeat a crafty Sorcerer and find their way back home!</desc>
		<releasedate>19921217T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Sega CS R&amp;D 2</developer>
		<publisher>Sega of America, Inc.</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
		<players>2</players>
		<lang>kr,en</lang>
	</game>
</gameList>
